<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Zodiac Archives - Manomay Jyotish</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/zodiac/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Manomay Jyotish</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 13:33:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/icon.jpg</url>
	<title>Zodiac Archives - Manomay Jyotish</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Jupiter Change &#8211; Mithun Rasa  &#124; Guru Maharaj &#124; Gemini Zodiac &#124;</title>
		<link>/jupiter-change-mithun-rasa-gemini/</link>
					<comments>/jupiter-change-mithun-rasa-gemini/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sneha Mane]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 05:30:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gemini]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Zodiac]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1058</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>  Hello! Welcome to Manomay Jyotish &#124; Manomay Jyotish and Vadhuvar , Satara &#124; मनोमय ज्योतिष  &#124; Gemini I am Professor Mrs.Sneha Mane warmly welcomes all the astrologers . Today we are seeing Horoscope of Gemini Zodiac . The planets keep on moving continuously. They enter from one zodiac sign to another through transits. They &#8230;</p>
<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="/jupiter-change-mithun-rasa-gemini/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Jupiter Change &#8211; Mithun Rasa  &#124; Guru Maharaj &#124; Gemini Zodiac &#124;</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/jupiter-change-mithun-rasa-gemini/">Jupiter Change &#8211; Mithun Rasa  | Guru Maharaj | Gemini Zodiac |</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Manomay Jyotish</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<script async="async" data-cfasync="false" src="//pl17043992.effectivecpmcontent.com/5ceee80be7b404130111bed642010939/invoke.js"></script>
<div id="container-5ceee80be7b404130111bed642010939"></div>


<div>
<figure id="attachment_2956" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-2956" style="width: 408px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://youtube.com/manomayjyotish" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img class="wp-image-2956" src="https://drjyotijoshi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/word-image-14.png" sizes="(max-width: 408px) 100vw, 408px" srcset="https://drjyotijoshi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/word-image-14.png 408w, https://drjyotijoshi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/word-image-14-300x300.png 300w, https://drjyotijoshi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/word-image-14-150x150.png 150w, https://drjyotijoshi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/word-image-14-100x100.png 100w" alt="Gemini | Guru | Jupiter | Astroguru " width="408" height="408" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-2956" class="wp-caption-text"><strong>Gemini | Guru | Jupiter | Astroguru | Horoscope | Rashifal</strong></figcaption></figure>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>Hello! Welcome to Manomay Jyotish | Manomay Jyotish and Vadhuvar , Satara | मनोमय ज्योतिष  | Gemini</strong></p>
<p><strong>I am Professor Mrs.Sneha Mane warmly welcomes all the astrologers . Today we are seeing Horoscope of Gemini Zodiac . The planets keep on moving continuously. They enter from one zodiac sign to another through transits. They have good or bad effect on human life. We are constantly analyzing these zodiac changes of the planets. Accordingly, in the coming April, all the planets are changing their zodiac signs. In this, the change of zodiac sign of Guru Maharaj, who is called a natural benefic planet, will be auspicious for all the zodiac signs in many ways. Because they are entering your voice. Guru Maharaj&#8217;s zodiac will change on 13th April and we are analyzing their effects according to the zodiac. In today&#8217;s episode how can we change this zodiac sign of Guru Maharaj for Gemini? We will discuss this in detail. #rashifal Rashifal </strong></p>
<p><strong>To understand this better, we have to first understand the information about Jupiter and its causation. Of all the planets, Moon, Mercury, Jupiter and Venus are the four natural benefic planets. However, the condition applies to the moon that the moon near the full moon is considered auspicious and the moon near the new moon is considered inauspicious. The farther the Moon is from the Sun, the further away it is from the houses. Apart from this, many conditions apply to the Moon from the point of view of auspiciousness. Mercury is also a natural benefic planet. However, the direction of its influence changes according to the planet with which it occurs. So somewhere there is a lack of his natural goodness. Then Jupiter and Venus are the only two auspicious planets left. Venus usually changes its zodiac within a month. That is, he gives all the good and bad results in a month. That is, the presence of Venus gives auspiciousness for small incidents. But Guru Maharaj stays in one zodiac for about 13 months. #Rashifal Rashifal</strong></p>
<p><strong>Also their vision has a lot to do with it. For all the other auspicious planets, the seventh is the only aspect. But Guru Maharaj has a total of three darshans named Pancham, Seventh and Navam. The important thing is that being a natural benefic planet, their vision is more important than the location. Actually their eyes are considered like nectar. In other words, Guru Maharaj has the power to stay in the zodiac for 13 months and also keep four places in the magazine in an auspicious way. According to the cause and effect of those four places, very auspicious results are given to the natives. That is why the change in the form of Guru Maharaj or his zodiac sign is very important. Now this is going to be especially important. Because since last three years of continuous negative, struggling journey, now they are going to start a pleasant journey. In our language, Guru Maharaj has been walking on rocky roads for the last three years. Even though he himself is on a rocky path, he has given as many auspicious results as he can. However, since his journey was in a state of conflict, it naturally affected the general public. Having entered their own Pisces, they will now begin their journey on a fine four-lane road. As a result, everyone will get their very auspicious results. In this way, Guru Maharaj is entering Pisces from Aquarius on 13th April. What will be the effect of this zodiac change on Gemini? Let us understand it now.</strong></p>
</div>


<script type="text/javascript">
	atOptions = {
		'key' : '3cc6993eb736f2fc864720745cf30f23',
		'format' : 'iframe',
		'height' : 60,
		'width' : 468,
		'params' : {}
	};
	document.write('<scr' + 'ipt type="text/javascript" src="http' + (location.protocol === 'https:' ? 's' : '') + '://www.highconvertingformats.com/3cc6993eb736f2fc864720745cf30f23/invoke.js"></scr' + 'ipt>');
</script>



<p><strong>When you think of Gemini, Guru Maharaj is the seventh lord and tenth lord of your zodiac. In other words, Guru Maharaja is the lord of Mithun or the two most important centers of marriage, the seventh and the tenth. That&#8217;s why Guru Maharaj is a very important planet for you and hence his zodiac sign is very important for you. For the past few months this has been your fate. Now these zodiac signs are going to change and enter your tenth place. In fact, Jupiter is not the significator of Gemini. Because he is the master of the two center places, he is to blame. Even so, owning one is still out of reach for the average person. Especially Guru Maharaja gets the responsibility of marital happiness, matrimonial partner, business, karma. In this way, Guru Maharaj will now enter your tenth place by changing the zodiac. Pisces is their source of water. Their position can be said to be very auspicious for Gemini natives.</strong></p>



<p><strong>The most important feature of Guru Maharaja in the tenth place is that there he will form Hansa Yoga which is one of the Panch Mahapurush Yoga. The most important thing is that this Raja Yoga is going to be formed at your place of Karma. When we think about the Kendra position, according to astrological laws, the fourth position is stronger than the first position. The seventh is considered to be the strongest position and the tenth is considered to be the strongest centre. One of the most auspicious planets in such a powerful center, Guru Maharaja and the Panchmahapurush Yoga created by him, Raja Yoga is one of the most important. Now Guru Maharaj will stay at your place of work for about thirteen months. This whole period will be very useful for starting your business, business security, business development, new business. This New Year will be especially beneficial for the people of Gemini zodiac who work in the field of education, writers and poets, those working in the field of management, new work in the field of education, studying in the field of education. . Research. #astroguru&nbsp; #guruparivartan #astrologer #horoscope</strong></p>



<html><script type="text/javascript">
	atOptions = {
		'key' : 'c202934202ba8ec5280eda3242cc0c9c',
		'format' : 'iframe',
		'height' : 50,
		'width' : 320,
		'params' : {}
	};
	document.write('<scr' + 'ipt type="text/javascript" src="http' + (location.protocol === 'https:' ? 's' : '') + '://www.highconvertingformats.com/c202934202ba8ec5280eda3242cc0c9c/invoke.js"></scr' + 'ipt>');
</script></html>



<p><strong>&nbsp;Guru Maharaj entering your tenth position will make your tenth position auspicious. At the same time, their vision will have a very good effect on you. We all know that Guru Maharaja has a total of three darshans namely Pancham, Seventh and Navam. The special thing is that their ideas are given more importance than places. Because their vision is considered to be nectar. Accordingly, the fifth vision of Guru Maharaj will fall in your second position in the tenth position. Then the seventh vision will come to the fourth position and the ninth vision will come to the sixth position. The second place in the magazine is called the place of wealth, family and speech. When Guru Maharaj&#8217;s nectar falls at this place, knowledge will flow through your speech. Which means it&#8217;s also going to be the most confusing time of the year. There will be money too. Because the second place is also the place of wealth. There are many ways in which you can earn money. Wealth will be created through karma, especially from your business. There will also be family happiness of the partner.</strong></p>



<p><strong>After this, the seventh sight of Guru Maharaj will fall on your fourth place. The fourth place in the magazine is called the place of happiness. From this various things like Vastu, Vehicle, Land, Happiness, Motherhood are seen. With the auspicious sight of Guru Maharaj at this place, there will be further increase in happiness, peace and prosperity in your home. Apart from this, very auspicious Vastu Yoga, Vehicle Yoga will also be formed for you. Therefore, the people of Gemini who have been dreaming of Vastu or Vehicle for many days, their dream will come true during this period. Those things will also be beneficial for you. Because that auspicious Yoga Guru Maharaj is going to create for you. The important thing is that during this time your Bhagya Shani Maharaj will also enter your destiny. A planet like Rahu will be in your benefic position and Guru Maharaj will be in your tenth position. Gemini sign people will get a lot of support from these three. Therefore, after the coming April month, Gemini native will make great progress in many areas, on many fronts. Of course, progress alone is not enough. If there is no happiness, prosperity, unity, love in your house, then money is useless. But during this time happiness, peace and love will be created in your house. There will be family happiness and wealth.</strong></p>



<p><strong>After this, the ninth sight of Guru Maharaj will fall on your sixth place. Health, job, debt, competitors, enemies are seen from the sixth position in the magazine. The result of having auspicious sight of Guru Maharaj at this place is that your enemies will automatically retreat or they will not have much enthusiasm in opposing you. Those who need loan can get it easily. It can also be beneficial for you. That is, it will be used for the same purpose for which you have taken it. The most important thing is that you will get good health during this period.</strong></p>



<p><strong>In short, Guru Maharaja, the creator of Hansa Yoga, will give you auspicious results in all directions. Enjoy it to the fullest. Actually, from now on there are going to be big changes in your life which are very positive, auspicious and beneficial. You should make full use of it. Live life to the fullest. Earn money the right way. Take proper care of your family and live a good life.</strong></p>



<p><strong>Talking about the remedies, astrology tells many small measures which can be easily done by anyone. There is no need to do anything special for this. Furthermore, even if the solution is small, the effect is huge. The only condition is that they should be dealt with with full confidence. According to this, considering the measures of Gemini, as it has been told earlier that Guru Maharaj is going to create Hans Yoga from the tenth position in your magazine. Therefore, the people of Gemini zodiac should help a young man in his business. Then you can guide him or help him. In short, he should cooperate for the prosperity of his business without any intention. Which will benefit you too.</strong></p>



<p><strong>Thus, I think this information is sufficient to understand the effect of Jupiter change on Gemini. So let&#8217;s stop here in today&#8217;s episode. In the next section we will study the effects on the next zodiac sign. So let&#8217;s see you in the next part. #astroguru&nbsp; &nbsp;#guruparivartan</strong></p>



<p><strong>Thank you!</strong></p>



<p><strong>Good luck!</strong></p>



<p><strong>Jyotish Pandit Mrs.Sneha Mane</strong></p>



<p><strong>More : <a href="/about-us/">About US</a> :&nbsp; <a href="https://youtube.com/manomayjyotish">Youtube </a>:&nbsp; <a href="/blog/">Blogs</a></strong></p>



<script type="text/javascript">
	atOptions = {
		'key' : 'e1a3efc8baee9f75248b8f0cb6c088bc',
		'format' : 'iframe',
		'height' : 300,
		'width' : 160,
		'params' : {}
	};
	document.write('<scr' + 'ipt type="text/javascript" src="http' + (location.protocol === 'https:' ? 's' : '') + '://www.highconvertingformats.com/e1a3efc8baee9f75248b8f0cb6c088bc/invoke.js"></scr' + 'ipt>');
</script>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/jupiter-change-mithun-rasa-gemini/">Jupiter Change &#8211; Mithun Rasa  | Guru Maharaj | Gemini Zodiac |</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Manomay Jyotish</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/jupiter-change-mithun-rasa-gemini/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
