<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>quotes on love Archives - Manomay Jyotish</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/quotes-on-love/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Manomay Jyotish</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 13:15:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/icon.jpg</url>
	<title>quotes on love Archives - Manomay Jyotish</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Love &#124; Find Your Real Love &#124; love quotes &#124; love story</title>
		<link>/find-your-boyfriend-and-girlfriend/</link>
					<comments>/find-your-boyfriend-and-girlfriend/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 12:46:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brandi love]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[good morning love]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[i love pdf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[i love you]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[love]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[love images]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[love quotes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[love quotes in english]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[love shayari]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[love shayari in hindi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[love status]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[love story]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[love wallpaper]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lover]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[quotes on love]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[romantic shayari]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[true love quotes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1000</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Find Your Love with Help of Astrology using all Zodiac Signs. Aries Mantra to keep your girlfriend happy. If your boyfriend or girlfriend has Aries zodiac sign, then you have got such a person who is stubborn, fearless, strong, courageous, quick, important. Your loved one is not a stranger but a kind of storm. With &#8230;</p>
<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="/find-your-boyfriend-and-girlfriend/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Love &#124; Find Your Real Love &#124; love quotes &#124; love story</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/find-your-boyfriend-and-girlfriend/">Love | Find Your Real Love | love quotes | love story</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Manomay Jyotish</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h2 class="has-text-align-center">Find Your Love with Help of Astrology using all Zodiac Signs.</h2>



<h3 class="has-text-align-center"><strong>Aries</strong></h3>



<p>Mantra to keep your girlfriend happy. If your boyfriend or girlfriend has Aries zodiac sign, then you have got such a person who is stubborn, fearless, strong, courageous, quick, important. Your loved one is not a stranger but a kind of storm. With that in mind, it&#8217;s hard to understand them, it&#8217;s hard for you to find a lifelong partner, since you are outspoken, outspoken, even if a little bitter, you will be happy to know that their love is sincere.</p>



<h3 class="has-text-align-center"><strong>Taurus</strong></h3>



<p><br>If your boyfriend or girlfriend is from Taurus then your boyfriend or girlfriend is from Taurus. This is their dream, their mind is immersed in love, the thought of constant love is wrapped around them, such a lover or lover loves beauty. Help them with their art skills, help them, sweethearts or lovers do not look back to compliment someone, they also always like to compliment, It is your destiny to find a happy person like Taro Tahi&#8217;s lover or a loving touch is enough.</p>



<h3 class="has-text-align-center"><strong>Gemini</strong></h3>



<p><br>If your boyfriend or girlfriend is Gemini then keep it happy! If your boyfriend or girlfriend is Gemini then you have to admit that you always stay happy and excited because your loved one is very handsome, these people are always thinking of you It is rare for them to make mistakes as they have very good skills, learn from sweet talkers, are very sweet and naughty, constantly win the hearts of others, Gemini lovers think of ways to keep their partner happy, and Dhammal is a fun joke. They also create such an environment, so if your loved one is in Gemini, always chat and have fun!</p>



<h3 class="has-text-align-center"><strong>Cancer</strong></h3>



<p><br>A person who is hungry for love is a person who is hungry for love. Cancer lovers are very loving, compassionate, emotional, affectionate, passionate, flowing in love. These lovers are anxious for love. If such a loving attitude is accompanied, then happiness becomes Mavenasa in the sky.</p>



<p>Cancer loved ones are open-minded and transparent, like water, create happiness and joy in the lives of others, give people the art of living a happy life, very sensitive happy philanthropist with a big heart. If accompanied, they remain happy.</p>



<h3 class="has-text-align-center"><strong>Leo</strong></h3>



<p><br>If a loved one is a Leo, then the person who has a flamboyant personality is a Leo, every Ada is like a king. It is as if Moden is a principle that will not bend, even in humiliation, these people are plates. Give!</p>



<h3 class="has-text-align-center"><strong>Virgo</strong></h3>



<p><br>How to keep your loved one happy if you are in Virgo? Virgo loved ones are always worried about your partner. They think about what they don&#8217;t want, their interests are always on top, their love never fails, it is difficult to find a person with a very loving and tender heart! No matter how many mistakes your mate may make, these people will show you the kindness, forgiveness, and peace they have, even though their tolerance is limited to a limited extent. These people are ready to help, the power to keep them happy is to call with love!</p>



<h3 class="has-text-align-center"><strong>Libra</strong></h3>



<p><br>If a loved one has a balance, then there is no one as lucky as you, your desire to seduce your lover hurts you. You consider yourself lucky to have found such a mate because of the art of sharing each other&#8217;s joys and sorrows, the attitude of understanding. If you want to make them happy, give them space and encourage them</p>



<h3 class="has-text-align-center"><strong>Scorpio</strong></h3>



<p><br>If your boyfriend or girlfriend is Scorpio, then this person does not apply the innermost thoughts, even though he is passionate, he is affectionate on the inside. It is necessary to understand the deep struggles in the minds of those who are angry, it is enough to encourage hard work, perseverance, perseverance.</p>



<h3 class="has-text-align-center"><strong>Sagittarius</strong></h3>



<p><br>If your loved one is Sagittarius, thank God there is no one as lucky as you. Happy, playful, philanthropic, optimistic, loving, gentle, intelligent, religious, humble, humble, compassionate, ideal king, all the qualities are found in Dharmaraja. . Support the good deeds they have so that they will be happy.</p>



<h3 class="has-text-align-center"><strong>Capricorn</strong></h3>



<p><br>If your loved one is Capricorn then there is a way to keep you happy. How to be happy in that situation, how to always be industrious No, even though they are not so passionate, a person who is aware of the reality wants to express true love in a simple way, their sadness needs love.</p>



<h3 class="has-text-align-center"><strong>Aquarius</strong></h3>



<p><br>If your boyfriend or girlfriend is Aquarius then the person is realistic, serious, intelligent, studious, serious in nature. Thoughtful nature gives importance to reality. Though not emotional, it is true in love.</p>



<h3 class="has-text-align-center"><strong>Pisces</strong></h3>



<p><br>If your loved one is Pisces then these people are very emotional, sensitive, always happy, loving nature, winning everyone&#8217;s heart, generous, temperament. The one who cares for others, who loves with all his heart, does not even know his whereabouts when he makes a home in the mind of others. People who are completely unaware of the very emotional reality love a person who has the same attitude of love as them. If you want to make this person happy, take care of them, love them from the heart.</p>



<p>Thanks for reading this <strong>blog</strong>!</p>



<p>Be sure to let us know your feedback.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/find-your-boyfriend-and-girlfriend/">Love | Find Your Real Love | love quotes | love story</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Manomay Jyotish</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/find-your-boyfriend-and-girlfriend/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
