<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Manomay Jyotish</title>
	<atom:link href="/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Manomay Jyotish</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2022 07:43:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/icon.jpg</url>
	<title>Manomay Jyotish</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>August 2022 Aries Horoscope &#8211; Next Month&#8217;s Aries Horoscope &#124; August Horoscope</title>
		<link>/aries-august-2022-horscope/</link>
					<comments>/aries-august-2022-horscope/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2022 07:37:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1139</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>General The month of August 2022 can give mixed results to the natives with the Aquarius zodiac sign. The presence of planets in your Kundli, especially, Sun, Venus, and Mercury will impact different aspects of your life. In the second week of the month, Venus and Sun will remain positioned in the fourth house in &#8230;</p>
<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="/aries-august-2022-horscope/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">August 2022 Aries Horoscope &#8211; Next Month&#8217;s Aries Horoscope &#124; August Horoscope</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/aries-august-2022-horscope/">August 2022 Aries Horoscope &#8211; Next Month&#8217;s Aries Horoscope | August Horoscope</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Manomay Jyotish</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<figure class="wp-block-post-featured-image"><img loading="lazy" width="375" height="375" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Aries-1.png" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="August 2022 Aries Horoscope &#8211; Next Month&#8217;s Aries Horoscope | August Horoscope" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Aries-1.png 375w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Aries-1-300x300.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/07/Aries-1-150x150.png 150w" sizes="(max-width: 375px) 100vw, 375px" /></figure>


<h2 class="has-text-align-center" id="General">General</h2>



<p><strong>The month of August 2022 can give mixed results to the natives with the Aquarius zodiac sign. The presence of planets in your Kundli, especially, Sun, Venus, and Mercury will impact different aspects of your life. In the second week of the month, Venus and Sun will remain positioned in the fourth house in Aries; as a result, you may be assigned new responsibilities at the workplace.</strong></p>



<p><strong> On the other hand, Saturn, the ruling lord of your deeds, being present in its own house may inspire you to work hard, and thus, you may get positive results. The month of August 2022 can be a bit challenging from a health point of view. You are likely to confront health-related problems because of the presence of Mercury, </strong></p>



<p><strong>the ruling of your sixth house, in the twelfth position from its own house. Let’s move forward and know what the month of August 2022 has on a platter for you.</strong></p>



<h2 class="has-text-align-center" id="Career">Career</h2>



<p><strong>From the career point of view, the month of August 2022 is likely to remain average for Aries. During this period, Saturn, the ruling lord of your tenth house, will stay in your tenth in a retrograde position after transiting from the eleventh house, due to which, you can be seen working hard for the success of your work. In the first half of the month, the work which has gone astray can come back because of the presence of Venus and Sun in your fourth house.</strong></p>



<p><strong> Owing to these two planets, new opportunities for employment will knock at your door. During this time, those natives who are looking for a job are likely to meet success. On the other hand, the period may prove to be approved for those who are associated or employed with foreign companies or those related to overseas business. </strong></p>



<p><strong>There is an excellent possibility that you may be fully rewarded for your labour. In the second half of the month, Sun will transit and form a conjunction with Mercury, leading to the formation of Budhaditya Yoga. During this time, there is a strong possibility of opening new employment opportunities for you.</strong></p>



<h2 class="has-text-align-center" id="Finance">Finance</h2>



<p><strong>If we see things from a financial point of view, the month of August 2022 is likely to be profitable for Aries. During this period, Venus, the ruling lord of your second house, the house of money or family, will reside in your fourth house, the house of comforts, with Sun, and thus, there can be an increase in your material pleasure</strong>.</p>



<p><strong> Along with this, you may also have financial gains. At the same time, you are likely to have full benefits of your labour due to the presence of Saturn, the ruling lord of the eleventh house, the house of profits, and tenth house, the house of Karma, in your tenth house. During this period, you can be seen faring well in your career. The income of service people is likely to increase</strong>.</p>



<p><strong> Those associated with the business may experience profitable times. However, you are suggested not to borrow or lend money because of the presence of Rahu with Mars in your first house in the same month i.e., August 2022 and if you do so, you may come across several challenges while returning or getting back the money. The period may be favourable for those engaged in foreign business. The natives of this zodiac sign may be successful in saving money and therefore, they will be financially sound.</strong></p>



<h2 class="has-text-align-center" id="Health">Health</h2>



<p><strong>So far the health of Aries people is concerned, the month of August 2022 is going to give mixed results. During this period, Mercury, the ruling lord of your sixth house, the house of disease, will be present in the twelfth house from its own house and as a result, the natives may confront health-related troubles. You are advised to avoid eating outside during this time. You may also suffer from venereal diseases. Too much exertion can create physical as well as mental problems. In such a situation, take out some time for yourself so that you can have some physical rest, otherwise, you may fall ill.</strong></p>



<p><strong> In this month, you will be seen helping others rather than taking care of yourself due to the aspect of Jupiter on your sixth house, the house of disease and this may impact your health adversely. In this regard, you are advised to pay equal heed to your health as well. In the second half of the month, the Sun will be present in your fifth house, due to which, you may be relieved of prolonged diseases. Seeing improvement in the health of elders, you may feel mentally comfortable.</strong></p>



<h2 class="has-text-align-center" id="Love/Marriage/Personal Relations">Love/Marriage/Personal Relations</h2>



<p><strong>The first fortnight of August 2022 is likely to be approved from the love angle for Aries. At the beginning of the month, Mercury, the significator of intelligence and communication, will be transiting in the fifth house, the house of children and education. Owing to this very reason, your relationship with your lover can be pleasant.</strong></p>



<p><strong> At the same time, Sun, the ruling lord of your fifth house, will form a conjunction with Venus in your fourth house, the house of comforts, and therefore, you are advised to have control over your language while interacting with your lover or spouse, otherwise, bitterness may crop up in your relations. </strong></p>



<p><strong>Try to sort things out amicably instead of frowning. Material pleasures in married life or love relationships may increase due to the presence of Venus, the benefactor of material pleasures, in your fourth house. The natives of the Aries zodiac sign should listen to the worries of their lover or spouse and try to understand their emotions. If Venus is strongly placed in your horoscope, the relations will bloom.</strong></p>



<h2 class="has-text-align-center" id="Family &amp; Friends">Family &amp; Friends</h2>



<p><strong>During the first fifteen days of the month, your family life may be comfortable due to the transit of Venus and Sun in your fourth house, the house of comforts and mother. During this time, love and affection among family members can increase and positive signs may be visible all around. Family members may ponder over resolving past conflicts through mutual discussions.</strong></p>



<p><strong> You can play a pivotal role to eradicate the problems occurring in your family life with your intelligence and maturity, as a result, a pleasant atmosphere may prevail in the family. Mercury, the ruling of your third house, is transiting in your fifth house, the house of children or education, and as a result, </strong></p>



<p><strong>your understanding with your father, and brothers, &amp; sisters is likely to strengthen. Married natives are likely to be benefitted from in-laws and your relationship with them may turn out better.</strong></p>



<h2 class="has-text-align-center" id="Advice">Advice</h2>



<p><strong>Recite the Bajrang Baan Path and offer Bhog to Lord Hanuman.<br>Offer Churma to Lord Hanuman.<br>Donate mustard oil in the Shani temple on Saturday.<br>Worship the Sun on Sunday.</strong></p>



<p><strong>Other : <a href="http://www.youtube.com/c/manomayjyotish">Youtube</a> : <a href="/">Home</a> : <a href="/about-us">About us</a> : <a href="https://goo.gl/maps/o3Z7wjSX9PWwsouB8">Google</a> : <a href="/services">Services</a></strong> </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/aries-august-2022-horscope/">August 2022 Aries Horoscope &#8211; Next Month&#8217;s Aries Horoscope | August Horoscope</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Manomay Jyotish</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/aries-august-2022-horscope/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>9 Online Dating STRATEGIES FOR Women: Tips &#038; Tricks TO CREATE Guys THINKING ABOUT You</title>
		<link>/9-online-dating-strategies-for-women-tips-tricks-to-create-guys-thinking-about-you/</link>
					<comments>/9-online-dating-strategies-for-women-tips-tricks-to-create-guys-thinking-about-you/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Trinidad]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 20:53:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[girl nude]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nudepussypics.com/college-pussy/ xxx]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1136</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#160;&#160; &#160;&#160;&#160;&#160; &#160;&#160; &#160;&#160; &#160;&#160; &#160;&#160; &#160;&#160;&#160;&#160; &#160;&#160; &#160;&#160;&#160;&#160; &#160;&#160; &#160;&#160;&#160;&#160; &#160;&#160;&#160;&#160; &#160;&#160; &#160;&#160; &#160;&#160; &#160;&#160; &#160;&#160;&#160;&#160; &#160;&#160; &#160;&#160;&#160;&#160; &#160;&#160; &#160;&#160;&#160;&#160; Web sites and apps. Who’d possess thought in this day and age that these will be the tools to assist you meet a guy? I’m continuously getting asked for online dating tips for women, &#8230;</p>
<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="/9-online-dating-strategies-for-women-tips-tricks-to-create-guys-thinking-about-you/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">9 Online Dating STRATEGIES FOR Women: Tips &#038; Tricks TO CREATE Guys THINKING ABOUT You</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/9-online-dating-strategies-for-women-tips-tricks-to-create-guys-thinking-about-you/">9 Online Dating STRATEGIES FOR Women: Tips &#038; Tricks TO CREATE Guys THINKING ABOUT You</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Manomay Jyotish</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul class="toc">
<li class="toc toc1"></li>
<li class="toc toc2">&nbsp;&nbsp;</li>
<li class="toc toc3">&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</li>
<li class="toc toc1"></li>
<li class="toc toc2">&nbsp;&nbsp;</li>
<li class="toc toc1"></li>
<li class="toc toc2">&nbsp;&nbsp;</li>
<li class="toc toc2">&nbsp;&nbsp;</li>
<li class="toc toc2">&nbsp;&nbsp;</li>
<li class="toc toc3">&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</li>
<li class="toc toc2">&nbsp;&nbsp;</li>
<li class="toc toc3">&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</li>
<li class="toc toc1"></li>
<li class="toc toc2">&nbsp;&nbsp;</li>
<li class="toc toc3">&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</li>
<li class="toc toc3">&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</li>
<li class="toc toc1"></li>
<li class="toc toc2">&nbsp;&nbsp;</li>
<li class="toc toc2">&nbsp;&nbsp;</li>
<li class="toc toc2">&nbsp;&nbsp;</li>
<li class="toc toc2">&nbsp;&nbsp;</li>
<li class="toc toc3">&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</li>
<li class="toc toc1"></li>
<li class="toc toc2">&nbsp;&nbsp;</li>
<li class="toc toc3">&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</li>
<li class="toc toc1"></li>
<li class="toc toc2">&nbsp;&nbsp;</li>
<li class="toc toc3">&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</li>
</ul>
<p><span style="display:block;text-align:center;clear:both"><img style="max-width: 530px;" src="https://purewows3.imgix.net/images/articles/2020_01/online_dating_tips_hero.jpg?auto\u003dformat,compress\u0026cs\u003dstrip" loading="lazy"></span>Web sites and apps. Who’d possess thought in this day and age that these will be the tools to assist you meet a guy? I’m continuously getting asked for online dating tips for women, so obviously it’s become this type of popular channel…and however women don’t really know how to own it.</p>
<p><span style="display:block;text-align:center;clear:both"><iframe loading="lazy" width="640" height="360" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/h8RklW9kGcY\u0026t=258s?rel=0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></span></p>
<p>Online dating differs from what happens once you meet someone organically. Individuals behave differently when they can hide behind technology. It could be challenging in order to read a man’s &#8220;body gestures&#8221; when you can’t in fact see his body!</p>
<h1>How To Make A Woman Chase You</h1>
<p>If you’ve just recently become single again, you may feel lost in this &#8221; new world &#8221; of dating through technology. It’s sort of scary, in fact. That’s why I put together this video and post filled with useful online dating strategies for women to assist you gain confidence in this new medium.</p>
<p><span style="display:block;clear:both;text-align:center"><strong><cite>Questions To Ask To Get To Know A Guy</cite></strong></span></p>
<p>Once you’ve mastered these tips, you’ll be dating online like a pro!</p>
<p>I don’t know about you, but I think internet dating shouldn’t be called online dating. It should be called &#8220;on the internet chatting in order to find an offline partnership.&#8221;</p>
<p>But that doesn’t sound as good…</p>
<p>But seriously, when you’re courting online, don’t allow yourself to fall into the trap of building an online connection.</p>
<p><span style="display:block;clear:both;text-align:center"><strong><cite>I Miss You More</cite></strong></span></p>
<p><img style="clear:both; float:left; padding:10px 10px 10px 0px;border:0px; max-width: 530px;" src="https://i0.wp.com/ferndate.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/best-dating-sites-for-portland-singles-1.jpg" loading="lazy">What I mean is: in the event that you invest so very much energy in talking to a guy for weeks online without meeting him, a) you merely have a pen pal and b) you&#8217;re putting yourself at critical emotional risk. And soon you meet a man personally, you can’t know for those who have chemistry. Definitely, you can &#8211; and should &#8211; become familiar with him through text message or chat before you even know if you need to meet him, but don’t let the chatting continue for too much time before you meet up with him.</p>
<div style="clear:both;"></div>
<p>Right after all, we’ve all heard of catfishing! And soon you meet a man face-to-face, how can you be sure he is really who he states he is? In 2011, the FBI Internet Crime Complaint Center acquired 5,600 complaints from victims of &#8220;romance scams.&#8221; And those are just the people reported. I have met countless women who&#8217;ve struck up a discussion with men online who, it turned out, were using someone else’s pictures and lying about everything.</p>
<p><span style="display:block;clear:both;text-align:center"><strong><cite>How To Respond To A Good Morning Text</cite></strong></span></p>
<p>Now I’m not stating this to scare you off. There are a ton of legit men on courting apps, and I know just as many women who&#8217;ve found great companions through internet dating. But I do need you to be cautious and meet this guy before you begin to get emotionally involved with him. Put your personal safety (and sanity) very first!</p>
<p>Okay, now it’s time for those online dating tips for women I promised you!</p>
<p>Online Dating Tips for Women #1: Keep Communications Short and Lovely</p>
<h2>Flirty Texts For Him</h2>
<p>Don’t create a book once you text him! Maintain it short.</p>
<h3>Casual Dating Meaning</h3>
<p>There’s a striking difference between how women message on dating apps and how men perform. Nearly all women will take enough time to learn a man’s profile and say something that shows they’re paying attention:</p>
<h1>How Do Guys Know When They Are Going To Come</h1>
<p>Hey Scott! I really like the pic with you on the mountain. Where were you?</p>
<p>Howdy Rob. I love ice fishing as well! I went to Alaska last year. Are you?</p>
<p>Men, however, don’t come up with something witty nearly normally. Many of them don’t also bother to learn that profile you meticulously wrote:</p>
<p><span style="display:block;clear:both;text-align:center"><strong><cite>Things Guys Like In Bed But Won&#8217;t Ask For</cite></strong></span></p>
<p>Hi sexy mama.</p>
<h2>Signs Of An Emotionally Unavailable Man</h2>
<p><img style='clear:both; float:left; padding:10px 10px 10px 0px;border:0px; max-width: 530px;' loading="lazy" src="https://www.truthforlife.org/static/uploads/daily_program/Jun6_2022_RelationshipsPart1of2.jpg" alt="">WTF?? How are you supposed to be impressed with a man who barely texts a whole sentence? Still, I’m likely to say that you should observe the brevity of men’s texts and perform exactly the same. You can say a lot more than hi, but don’t go overboard telling your daily life story when you first start messaging in the dating app.</p>
<div style="clear:both;"></div>
<p>The conversation should be two-sided, so constantly end your response with a question to keep the conversation heading.</p>
<p>I work in technologies as a project manager. What now ??</p>
<p>I saw you detailed photography as a spare time activity. What do you like taking pictures of?</p>
<p>Also, remember that texting actually isn’t the best way to get to know someone, which means that your goal should be to can get on the phone with this guy.  In case you have any inquiries with regards to where and also how you can use <a href="http://www.nudepussypics.com/pussy-panties/">www.nudepussypics.com/pussy-panties-photos</a>, you are able to e-mail us on the page. Yes, we’ve moved away from talking on the telephone just as much (a shame, in my mind), but talking to a guy you’re considering going out with can help give you a better feeling of whether he’s a good suit for you, and you may talk faster than you can type, to get to know one another faster.</p>
<h1>How To Know If Your Attractive</h1>
<p>Psychotherapist and author of The Relationship Fix, Dr. Jenn Mann states: &#8220;For those who have met somebody on a dating app, the most common protocol is to first text and then talk on the phone before asking somebody on a date. It is important to see if there is good talking chemistry before conference in person. Nearly all women sense safer after talking on the telephone first.&#8221;</p>
<p>Keep those messages short so that you can motivate him to actually dial you once you provide him your quantity.</p>
<p><span style="display:block;clear:both;text-align:center"><strong><cite>He Loves Me</cite></strong></span></p>
<p>P.S. If you’re a little nervous in what to text, exercise on MeetMe. It’s a dating app that’s actually text-centric. What have you got to lose?</p>
<p>Online Dating Strategies for Women #2: See Online Dating simply because a Marathon, Not just a Sprint</p>
<p>It’s an easy task to get disheartened after a few weeks of using dating apps without great results. You might have great conversations with males you find attractive, only for them to ghost. You may continue dates with duds. You might find nobody that sparks curiosity. You might feel rejected if you get few communications.</p>
<h2>What Does Clingy Mean</h2>
<p>I require you to know: that is all part of it. Online courting is a tool to find interesting people, not a magic wand that will instantly fulfill your desire to have a boyfriend. Also it takes work. Like everyone else have to make an application for dozens of tasks when you’re looking for a career move just to get yourself a few interviews and hopefully a minumum of one job give, you’ve got to place in the time on dating apps to make it work.</p>
<p><span style="display:block;clear:both;text-align:center"><strong><cite>Bumble First Message</cite></strong></span></p>
<p>Some websites prioritize the profiles of people who are online, so if you save money time online, you’ll have more results.</p>
<h2>Topics To Talk About With Your Boyfriend</h2>
<p>Look at going in dates, even if they don’t work out, as practice. Especially if you’ve been out of the dating game a while, you can benefit from texting, speaking with, and going out with men.</p>
<p>Online Dating Tips for Women #3: Make Him Come to You</p>
<h2>Man In Your Dreams</h2>
<p>He should be ready to arrived at you for a romantic date.</p>
<p>One of the best online dating tips for women that I can offer is to understand that you&#8217;re a prize to be gained. Which means he drives to meet you, not the other way around. Select a restaurant or restaurant close to your home so that you put in minimal effort to go on this very first meetup.</p>
<p>However, do NOT have him choose you up at your house!</p>
<p>On a first date (really 1st meet), you don’t understand this guy sufficiently to trust him together with your address. Once again, safety ought to be your top worry. Don’t provide him your contact number early on either, because he can use that to find your address.</p>
<h3>What Does Fwb Mean</h3>
<p>Creepy.</p>
<h2>Don&#8217;t Ask Me About My Ex</h2>
<p>(An alternative to giving your number is by using a phone and messaging app which means that your contact number is shielded.)</p>
<h3>7 Obvious Signs He Likes You</h3>
<p>If he’s not willing to drive, screw him. You don’t want a guy who’s not willing to put in a little effort to meet you.</p>
<p>Online Dating Tips for Women #4: Believe He’s 50% Much less Attractive Than His Photos</p>
<h1>Dirty Texts To Send</h1>
<p>Look, we all take action. We put our greatest pictures online. Hell, some people even doctor our photos to make us look even better than we actually look!</p>
<p><span style="display:block;clear:both;text-align:center"><strong><cite>Signs He&#8217;s Falling In Love</cite></strong></span></p>
<p>Men may post pics from high school because they’re too embarrassed to post recent pics that show they’re balding and overweight. It’s silly, because obviously, you’re going to find that out once you meet him, but he’s hoping you’ll possess fallen madly for him at that time and will forget the little white lie of photos that don’t very tell the whole story.</p>
<p>There’s furthermore the opposite situation to understand: some guys just take bad photos. They’re not the selfie queens that women can be, so they can be clueless when it comes to posting photos that actually look good. If you adored this article and you would certainly like to receive more facts concerning  (<a href="https://www.psychologytoday.com/us/blog/the-nature-nurture-nietzsche-blog/201005/why-do-men-cheat">www.psychologytoday.com/us/blog/the-nature-nurture-nietzsche-blog/201005/why-do-men-cheat</a>) kindly browse through our web page.</p>
<h2>Biggest Turn Offs For Girls</h2>
<p>So another internet dating tip? Don’t place so much stock in his pictures. He’ll look different in person, therefore if he seems actually remotely attractive, he might be even more so in person. If the info in his profile interests you, it’s worth learning him. Worst situation is he ends up just being a friend.</p>
<p><span style="display:block;clear:both;text-align:center"><strong><cite>Why Do Guys Ghost Girls</cite></strong></span></p>
<p>Online Dating Strategies for Women #5: Do not Lie</p>
<h3>Signs He Likes You More Than You Think</h3>
<p>One of the greatest online dating strategies for women:  <a href="https://legalcannabisoils.com/uncategorized/when-is-the-right-time-to-begin-what-turns-men-on/">www.nudepussypics.com/top-housewife-pussy/</a> be truthful!</p>
<p>If you expect a guy to be honest with you, whether it’s by displaying photos that accurately portray him or being real in his profile, how can you expect to get away with lying yourself?</p>
<p>And yet, 54% of individuals lie on their dating profiles!</p>
<p>It really goes back to the confidence matter: if you are protected in who you are, there’s simply no reason you should fudge your web dating profile. You’re a sexy, rockin’ lady, and any man would be happy to get the chance to get you out.</p>
<p>Online Dating Strategies for Women #6: Do not Be Shy With That Block Button</p>
<p><span style="display:block;clear:both;text-align:center"><strong><cite>I Love My Man</cite></strong></span></p>
<p>We wish I could say that each man who tries to get your attention online is a quality dude, but the reality is, there are a lot of scummy men out there. I said it earlier: people prefer to hide behind technology. They feel they can say things they might never say to that person because there’s a degree of anonymity on the web.</p>
<p>But remember: you are in control. You do not have to put up with men’s bad habits online.</p>
<h3>How To Be A Better Boyfriend</h3>
<p>If a guy supplies you with sketchy photos…</p>
<h1>How To Get A Man</h1>
<p>If his starting line will be what’s your preferred position?</p>
<p>If he just plain creeps you out…</p>
<h2>How To Start Conversation With A Guy Over Text</h2>
<p>BLOCK.</p>
<h2>Does He Love You</h2>
<p>Online Dating Strategies for Women #7: Prequalify Him Before Meeting</p>
<p>Make sure he meets the needs you have before going in a date.</p>
<h2>Attractively Bold Self Assurance</h2>
<p>While several tips ago We told you never to spend too much time online with this guy before conference him, I absolutely encourage one to have prerequisites that you can choose a man is in fact worth meeting. Again, you have all the power, therefore decide what’s important to you. </p>
<h2>How To Seduce A Man</h2>
<p>Here certainly are a few examples of what I’m talking about when I say you have to prequalify him:</p>
<p>You want to have had a telephone call before you satisfy (then you can tell if he&#8217;s got an annoyingly shrill voice and save the trouble of meeting him in person).</p>
<p>You desire a man who asks you queries, not just talks about himself.</p>
<p>You would like a man who will take initiative and texts you regularly.</p>
<h3>Relationship Questions To Ask A Guy</h3>
<p>You want to know at least basics about him, like where he works, maybe high-level details about past relationships (divorced? children?),  <a href="https://blogalma.com/dont-waste-time-5-facts-to-start-hot-sexting/">nudepussypics.com/dildo-in-pussy/</a> and what he’s looking for.</p>
<p>Make a list of these requirements and before you consent to meet, make sure the man hits everything on your own list.</p>
<p>But also recognize that you don’t need to know everything about this guy before you meet him. That’s what makes those early dates therefore much fun: once you sit in person and get to know one another, you’re already needs to bond. So don’t change your beginning texts into an inquisition! Conserve something for later on.</p>
<h1>How To Keep A Man Interested</h1>
<p>And if he pushes one to meet sooner than you’re ready, you almost certainly won’t such as this guy in any case. Don’t agree to meet up with him until you’re ready.</p>
<p>Online Dating Tips for Women #8: Consider The First Date a First Meet</p>
<p>I tell my clients this on a regular basis: a first online date is NOT a date. It’s a first &#8220;meetup&#8221;. Here’s how I start to see the difference:</p>
<p><img src='https://www.quotemaster.org/images/1b/1b6644555c170982c7a139db47a2954b.jpg' loading='lazy' style='clear:both; float:left; padding:10px 10px 10px 0px;border:0px; max-width: 530px;'>A day happens between two different people who already know they have chemistry and like one another.</p>
<div style="clear:both;"></div>
<p>A meetup is what you do to observe when you have that chemistry. Chatting on the web isn&#8217;t the same thing as being in one another’s existence, and without being together in person, you can’t know if there’s opportunity for a partnership to blossom.</p>
<p>In an article on Bustle about chemistry, relationship and dating professional Margaux Cassuto said:</p>
<p>&#8220;Romantic chemistry can be an effortless attraction between two different people that can feel magnetic and addictive. It’s to blame for many 2nd dates. It can come in the form of a physical, psychological, as well as intellectual bond. Scientists believe that chemistry is because the chemicals in the human brain determining compatibility.&#8221;</p>
<p>Shifting your mindset from &#8220;date&#8221; to &#8220;meet&#8221; can take a few of the pressure away from. Have absolutely zero goals about meeting a man you’ve been talking to online. Even though you two strike it off via text message, you don’t understand that you will strike it off romantically. You’re just two different people meeting over espresso. If the conversation takes off, great. If not, give it one hour, shake his hands, and move on with your life.</p>
<h2>Signs Someone Is In Love With You</h2>
<p>Online Dating Tips for Women #9: Possess a feeling of Humor</p>
<h3>Boyfriend Good Morning Text For Him</h3>
<p>Allow him to cause you to laugh!</p>
<h1>Stages Of Love</h1>
<p>Men like women with a sense of humor. Research released in the Journal of Psychology showed that individuals with a feeling of humor were rated more attractive than others. Therefore if you’re witty, allow it shine both in your web dating user profile and in your texts.</p>
<h2>Is He Playing Me</h2>
<p>Keep in mind that,  <a href="https://dongyphuckhangan.vn/how-to-quickly-get-over-someone-you-wont-ever-dated-and-move-ahead-next/">Brazilian pussy</a> especially in early stages, you&#8217;re being assessed in everything that you say. In the event that you had a negative day and actually want to vent about it, recognize that you don’t understand this man well enough to do therefore, and you might arrive off as negative if you do. Instead, find a way to make light of your bad day.</p>
<p>Him: How was your entire day?</p>
<p><span style="display:block;clear:both;text-align:center"><strong><cite>How To Talk Dirty To A Man</cite></strong></span></p>
<p>You: Oh, you know. The normal. Had a set tire. Spilled my coffee around me. If I makes it to bed without getting stepped on by a semi, I’ll consider today a success!</p>
<h3>Good Questions To Ask A Guy</h3>
<p>And tell him that he’s funny! Males love making you laugh, and it’s a great indicator that you’re interested.</p>
<p>Hopefully, these internet dating tips for women show you that dating apps and web sites aren’t something to be feared, but something to have fun with. Don’t go on it so seriously! Enjoy the sport of flirting on-line and looking at pictures and profiles of warm guys.</p>
<p>And don’t rely solely on internet dating to meet a man! Get out there and participate in activities or head to areas where you’re more likely to meet men to increase your opportunity.</p>
<p>What has your knowledge with internet dating been? Are you experiencing other online dating tips for women to pass along in the feedback below?</p>
<p><span style="display:block;text-align:center;clear:both"><img style="max-width: 530px;" src="https://orion-uploads.openroadmedia.com/md_7aaf6634cf1f-jeremy-bishop-206722.jpg" loading="lazy"></span></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/9-online-dating-strategies-for-women-tips-tricks-to-create-guys-thinking-about-you/">9 Online Dating STRATEGIES FOR Women: Tips &#038; Tricks TO CREATE Guys THINKING ABOUT You</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Manomay Jyotish</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/9-online-dating-strategies-for-women-tips-tricks-to-create-guys-thinking-about-you/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Aries Horoscope July 2022 Horoscope in Hindi &#124; Mesh Rashi Aries July 2022 Horoscope &#124;</title>
		<link>/aries-july-2022/</link>
					<comments>/aries-july-2022/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 09:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1131</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Mesh Rashi Aries July 2022 Horoscope &#124; Ups and downs come in the life of every person and their solution is possible with the right guidance, so let us solve your every problem. Hello. First of all, if we know about the fasting and festivals coming in this month of July, then on July 13, &#8230;</p>
<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="/aries-july-2022/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Aries Horoscope July 2022 Horoscope in Hindi &#124; Mesh Rashi Aries July 2022 Horoscope &#124;</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/aries-july-2022/">Aries Horoscope July 2022 Horoscope in Hindi | Mesh Rashi Aries July 2022 Horoscope |</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Manomay Jyotish</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h3 class="has-text-align-center"><strong> Mesh Rashi Aries July 2022 Horoscope |</strong></h3>


<figure class="wp-block-post-featured-image"><img width="500" height="500" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/chakra-1.png" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Aries Horoscope July 2022 Horoscope in Hindi | Mesh Rashi Aries July 2022 Horoscope |" loading="lazy" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/chakra-1.png 500w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/02/chakra-1-300x300.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/02/chakra-1-150x150.png 150w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/02/chakra-1-96x96.png 96w" sizes="(max-width: 500px) 100vw, 500px" /></figure>


<p><br><strong>Ups and downs come in the life of every person and their solution is possible with the right guidance, so let us solve your every problem. Hello. First of all, if we know about the fasting and festivals coming in this month of July, then on July 13, the festival of Guru Purnima is coming and this festival is dedicated to the Guru. A person&#8217;s life without a Guru is like a boat that is rudderless and cannot reach the shore. That is why if there is no guru in your life, then definitely make a guru in your life. On July 28, the festival of Hariyali Amavasya i.e. Shravan Amavasya will be celebrated with great pomp. Donating fruits of drinks and fruits on this day is especially beneficial and on July 31, the festival of Hariyali Teej will be celebrated by all the married people. This festival is kept by the honeymooners for the long life of their honey. So here are the special fasts and festivals coming in this month which are making this month of July even more special. Aries Horoscope July 2022</strong></p>



<p><strong>If we move ahead and know how this month is going to be important according to the position of the planets, then Sun, which is currently sitting in its friendly sign Gemini, and on July 16, they will enter their very friendly zodiac Cancer. The planet Mercury which is currently sitting in its very friendly zodiac sign Taurus. They will enter their own zodiac sign Gemini at the beginning of the month i.e. on 2nd July. That is, even after going there, they will be self-occupied and after that on July 17, they will again sit in their even zodiac sign Cancer, after changing the zodiac. Even when Sun and Mercury are placed in Gemini, they will still form Budhaditya Yoga and after that in Cancer also they will be seen forming Budhaditya Yoga after half a month. The planet Mars will remain self-occupied throughout this month in its own zodiac sign Aries, which is also your zodiac lord. The planet Jupiter will be sitting in its own zodiac sign Pisces as a self-occupied person for the whole month. Venus is currently in its own zodiac sign Taurus and on July 13, it will enter its very friendly sign, Gemini. The planet Saturn is currently sitting in its original triangle sign Aquarius this month and on July 12, after changing the zodiac, it will again become self-gratified in Capricorn. Rahu will remain in his even sign Aries for the whole month and Ketu will remain in his own sign Libra for the whole month. The month of July is also very important according to the planets because the influence of the huge planets Saturn and Saturn remains very much on our life and on 12th July Saturn is going retrograde. They are going to Capricorn again and as soon as they go to Capricorn, they will again feel dhaiya in Gemini and Virgo and Sagittarius since Saturn&#8217;s half-century has been removed. Again, Saturn&#8217;s Sati is going to be felt for the people of Sagittarius, then there is a change in the zodiac sign of Saturn, it is going to be very important and important for all the zodiac signs. However, in this month, four planets are sitting as self-possessed, in which Guru Shani, Mars and Venus will be sitting in this month as self-occupied. In which Venus is going to sit as an ascetic for half a month, that is, to sit as a four-and-a-half-year-old and the big planet Saturn&#8217;s zodiac changes back to Capricorn, will this affect your life this month? Let&#8217;s know about him Aries Horoscope July 2022 Horoscope in Hindi</strong></p>



<p><strong>Let&#8217;s start with the monthly horoscope of Aries for the month of July, this is the amount we are giving you, it is based on the lunar calculations and is equally effective according to both your zodiac and ascendant, then first of all know. About your zodiac lord i.e. about Mars, which is sitting in your own zodiac sign i.e. Aries, as a self-gracious person for this whole month. Although Rahu is forming Angarak Yoga by sitting with Mars, then he will try to suppress Mars somewhere. If the yoga is not so good then you have to be a little careful in your work. Only with more hard work you will get positive positive results for yourself. As you are moving towards achieving your goal, then tireless hard work is necessary for you and this month you will also have to make tireless efforts. However, at this time you will have to keep aggression and anger in your side because Mars is sitting in your sign and making you Manglik, which can increase your anger and aggression and because of this misunderstanding can be created. Wrong decision can be made in haste and because of that you can also see situations of loss. So avoid taking wrong decision in your personality. If someone tries to mislead or mislead you, then you do not have to come in his words. Do not take any decision in a hurry while using your discretion and intelligence. There can be ups and downs in relationship with father-in-law. In this way, proceed with the relationship with them thoughtfully. You may have an argument, especially with a cousin or with uncle, with aunt, with Tauji, there may be a dispute. Disputes may arise regarding any other matter regarding ancestral property. Therefore, to avoid these situations at this time, you need to have a lot of restraint on your speech and control of anger. Personality is going to be very good. Since Mars is your zodiac lord, he will increase your might and give you very good success in the technical field.Will give But at this time, with your speech and with your anger, you can spoil the works made by you. In this case you need to be very much aware. Aries Horoscope July 2022</strong></p>



<p><strong>Now the eighth lord is your Mars which is also your zodiac lord. According to the eighth house, you will have to be careful from your secret enemies. However, they will not be able to harm you. If your zodiac lord is sitting in a very powerful position, then you will defeat every person who is trying to harm you in some way or the other, but still you need to be careful. Do not get emotional and keep your confidential things to yourself and confidential documents in a safe place. Avoid secret enemies who may be your relatives. May be friends, may be colleagues, may be neighbors. There could be any person in your circle, so stay a little bit away from such people. Avoid wrong investments during this time. You will end up getting a little confused. That is, your mind will wander a little and you should control the situations of this disorientation so that you can avoid wrong decisions. Avoid wrong investments or else the situations of loss may increase. You may have to take a loan from someone. You can also get secret money during this time. That too remains a strong possibility. Try to do your tasks in a normal way. Do not put your hands in risky activities at all.</strong></p>



<p><strong>Now let&#8217;s talk about the second house in the second place, which is the house of wealth, its owner is Venus, which is sitting in its own house as a self-occupied person and is going to stay there till July 13. For about half a month, Venus being your second lord, sitting in your own house, will increase your happiness resources. Will get ancestral property. Your profit positions will increase progressively during this time. At this time, if you do any work related to Venus, whether it is travel business, whether it is film industry or any work related to art. Whether it is work related to restaurant food. Be it any work related to fragrance related to flowers i.e. perfume related. This time is going to be wonderful for the people related to such works, because on July 13, when Venus will change the zodiac, even then it will revolve around a planet from itself, then the second lord will sit one house ahead of itself and since Venus is your seventh lord, then he Your actions in your business will definitely bring good profit situations in your business. When Venus will go one house ahead of itself and sit in Gemini, that is, it will sit in your mighty house. Then they will also combine with Parakramesh and your Panchmesh, then this time period of four to five days, that is, this time period from July 13 to 16, 17, it is going to be very good for you. In these three days, you will see situations of big profit. Any big work will be completed successfully for you. In some big work, your might will be seen increasing by ending the situations of stagnation. You may receive a large order at this time. That is, there is a possibility of some big event happening with you. Venus is sitting in the seventh house and Ketu is in the seventh house, so you have to walk a little cautiously. Especially in married life, if the marriage relationship is not going well, then it can be broken. Be a little careful. You can also get cheated in love relationship. So get to know the full details about your partner. After that, be serious and proceed with that relationship more seriously because if you have made haste, then after that you will not feel anything other than sadness, depression. You will be seen getting invitations fast in marriage relations. If you have become marriageable, then do not rush at all while selecting your life partner. Keep this in mind a little bit. Aries Horoscope July 2022</strong></p>



<p><strong>Now coming to the third place, the lord of your third house is Mercury, which is the lord of your disease house and the mighty sitting in his own house, you will also get relief in diseases which can be related to Mercury. You have to forget things again and again. There is a problem related to the nervous system, whether it is hair fall or memory loss. All these problems will now appear to be diminishing a bit. Mercury&#8217;s results will be very good. Even later, when Mercury will change its zodiac and move to Cancer on July 17, you will still see better results of Mercury. Anyway, Sun is becoming Budhaditya Yoga of Mercury and since Sun is your fifth lord, then you will get to see the combination of Panchmesh and Parakramesh throughout the month. That is, even in Gemini, Sun and Mercury will be together and after that they are going to sit together in Cancer, forming Budhaditya Yoga, so this combination of Sun and Mercury is going to be very good for the student class. If you want to take any important decision, then definitely take it. This time is going to be very good for you for those decisions, but after taking advice from an experienced person, you should go ahead in this season. Do not take any decision in a hurry and overconfident. Your hold in politics will increase and your political dominance will be seen increasing. Your union with siblings will make your tuning look much better and better. The relations which were spoiled, those relations will now be resolved and sweetness will be seen in those relations. You will be very happy with the relationship. older siblings at this time. From here you will get full support and their complete guidance. You will get benefit in health related problems. No matter how hard the enemy side may try against you. They will not be able to put obstacles in your work to obstruct your work. You will be successful in defeating your enemies by working with your intelligence and tact, your alertness. At this time your six senses will be very strong and due to the power of thinking, you will defeat your opponents in a logical way. They will be seen closing their mouths. Aries Horoscope July 2022</strong></p>



<p><strong>Now we come to the fourth house, which we also call the place of happiness. The lord of that house is the Moon, which changes the zodiac very quickly in two and half days in two and a half days, but Sun and Mercury sitting in your happiness and creating Budhaditya Yoga. This time period is going to be very good for you. happiness will increase. Will increase luxury. Happiness Resources You will be seen doing electronic items, home maintenance or shopping for a luxury vehicle at this time. You can do property at this time and your matters related to the purchase and sale of property will be resolved very soon. At this time your financial condition will be very strong and you will be seen in your financial form. Your financial side will be very strong and because of that, you will think of doing something new in your work, making some new investments and implementing new plans. That is, according to the moon, this time will also be seen giving you the best results. Sometimes there will be ups and downs, but due to Budhaditya Yoga of Sun and Mercury, you will get to see the situation of good profit this month. Aries Horoscope July 2022</strong></p>



<p><strong>Now we have come to the Cham house, the Sun is the fifth lord, we have told you earlier also that the Budhaditya yoga of Sun and Mercury will be formed in the mighty house and in the center the Budhaditya yoga of Sun and Mercury will be formed. According to that, it is good, but till July 16, the fifth lord will give you very good results because the fifth lord will go to the 11th and sit on the eleventh and sit in conjunction with the mighty, then this time is very good for the student class. Those students associated with Vidya studies, especially those who are students associated with the medical field or those who have taken Bio, time is going to be very good for them and this time will increase the progress and progress of the students more and will increase your sphere of influence. . At this time you will be seen becoming the face of the teacher and the principal.</strong></p>



<p><strong> At this time you will take any work in hand. You will definitely get success in it. You will be seen doing well in art in debate. Your writing will become more effective. At this time if you participate in any essay competition. If you participate in the debate, then this time will bring you great success. He will leave only after getting a medal. Time will be full of respect and fame for the people associated with the literary world. You will definitely be appreciated in whatever work you do during this time. [ Aries ] If you were worried about his career till now, then get rest now. He will be seen getting settled in his career at this time.</strong></p>



<p><strong>Now come, if you talk about the place of luck at your place of luck, then if you talk about Bhagyesh, then this month is going to be very wonderful for you. Children who want to go out to study for higher education or want to get scholarship from outside college or you want to do some job by going to outside college, then surely your work will be completed successfully. For the students associated with the field of management or for the people associated with the field of management, this is the time to move forward in the career. There will be something new and good to do in career. At this time your wishes will be fulfilled and you will appear very successful living in your field. As a brand name becomes yours, one will be seen becoming your fame. Guru will also take you towards spirituality. At this time, your interest in religious activities will increase and make the outline of religious rituals. Taking active part in religious rituals, such activities will intensify you at this time. That is, you will be seen moving more towards spirituality. At this time, you will definitely be seen achieving success in your work. You will also be associated with works like dharma karma, human service, which will increase your social honor and respect. Aries</strong></p>



<p><strong>Now since Guru is the lord of your twelfth house. The Guru is sitting in his own house, being self-occupied. Will control expenses. A management will make you strong. You will come to know how to manage the budget[ Aries ]. This time will make you more empowered. Will match. At this time your decisions will be correct. You can take your decision very calmly and discreetly. Your Mars which is the lord of the zodiac is sitting in your place. Do not use anger and passion, but act with discretion and intelligence and after that take any decision. Although the Guru will stop you from time to time from taking the wrong decision from the aggressive, then you must listen to the voice of your soul in your mind. Aries Horoscope July 2022</strong></p>



<p><strong>Now we come to the tenth house, which is the lord of karmic house, which is going to change the zodiac sign of Shani, which is going to change the big zodiac this month and till now he was sitting in your profit house and now your karmic place Coming in and becoming self-confident and sitting again. Will be Saturn&#8217;s retrograde is a bit like this, which is the time of change of zodiac. On 12th July, which Saturn is going to come in your karmic house, at this time you have to be more alert. Be careful while driving. There may be a problem related to bones. Be very careful and alert towards him. Avoid taking any big decision during this time.[ Aries ] Anyway, you should do the same tasks in which your work is going on. Keep rapport with colleagues in the workplace as coordination with them can be a bit up-and-down. Do any work by taking your boss into confidence. However, the officers will be happy with you. Employed people will definitely get the fruits of their hard work, but do not take any hasty decisions due to aggression and anger. Avoid taking decisions in haste. Shani is the lord of your Aquarius sign and he will remain in your Aquarius sign till 12th July till mother. Will sit in profit house. Sitting in the house of profit will get very good results in situations of your profit. Anyway, we told you that you are going to be very strong this month. This time will also be of promotion increment for the employed people. At this time, if you want to switch your job, then this time has become very good for that too, so if we talk about overall, then this month is going to be very good and full of beneficial results for the people of Aries.</strong></p>



<p><strong>Other : <a href="/about-us">About us</a> : <a href="/">Home </a>: <a href="/blog">Blogs</a> : <a href="https://youtube.com/c/manomayjyotish">Youtube</a></strong></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/aries-july-2022/">Aries Horoscope July 2022 Horoscope in Hindi | Mesh Rashi Aries July 2022 Horoscope |</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Manomay Jyotish</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/aries-july-2022/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Jupiter Change &#8211; Kumbh Raas &#124; Aquarius zodiac &#124;</title>
		<link>/jupiter-change-aquarius-rashi/</link>
					<comments>/jupiter-change-aquarius-rashi/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 12:15:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1113</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Aquarius Zodiac karma will increase economic profit opportunities   Hello! I am Pro.Mrs. Sneha Mane warmly welcomes all the astrologers and people. &#124; Aquarius Zodiac &#124; Planets travel continuously. They enter from one zodiac sign to another through transits. They have good or bad effect on human life. We are constantly analyzing these zodiac changes &#8230;</p>
<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="/jupiter-change-aquarius-rashi/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Jupiter Change &#8211; Kumbh Raas &#124; Aquarius zodiac &#124;</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/jupiter-change-aquarius-rashi/">Jupiter Change &#8211; Kumbh Raas | Aquarius zodiac |</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Manomay Jyotish</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="vJOb1e Pw4Ldf RsCEN akVW1d" role="text">
<div class="iRPxbe">
<div class="mCBkyc tNxQIb ynAwRc nDgy9d" role="heading" aria-level="4"><strong>Aquarius <span style="font-size: 1rem; color: var(--ast-global-color-3); background-color: var(--ast-global-color-5);">Zodiac</span></strong></div>
</div>
</div>
<div>
<p><strong>karma will increase</strong></p>
<p><strong>economic profit opportunities</strong></p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-3247" src="https://drjyotijoshi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/word-image-22.png" sizes="(max-width: 408px) 100vw, 408px" srcset="https://drjyotijoshi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/word-image-22.png 408w, https://drjyotijoshi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/word-image-22-300x300.png 300w, https://drjyotijoshi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/word-image-22-150x150.png 150w, https://drjyotijoshi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/word-image-22-100x100.png 100w" width="408" height="408" /></p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>Hello!</strong></p>
<p><strong>I am Pro.Mrs. Sneha Mane warmly welcomes all the astrologers and people. | <span style="color: var(--ast-global-color-3); font-size: 1rem; background-color: var(--ast-global-color-5);">Aquarius Zodiac </span>| Planets travel continuously. They enter from one zodiac sign to another through transits. They have good or bad effect on human life. We are constantly analyzing these zodiac changes of the planets. Accordingly, all the planets are changing their zodiac signs in the coming April. In this, the change of zodiac sign of Guru Maharaj, who is called a natural benefic planet, will be auspicious for all the zodiac signs in many ways. Because they are entering your voice. Guru Maharaj&#8217;s zodiac will change on 13th April and we are analyzing their effects according to the zodiac. In today&#8217;s episode how can we change this sign of Guru Maharaj to Aquarius? We will discuss this in detail. | Aquarius Zodiac |</strong></p>
<p><strong>To understand this better, we have to first understand the information about Jupiter and its causation. Of all the planets, Moon, Mercury, Jupiter and Venus are known as the four natural benefic planets. However, the condition applies to the moon that the moon near the full moon is considered auspicious and the moon near the new moon is considered inauspicious. The farther the Moon is from the Sun, the further away it is from the houses. Apart from this, many conditions apply to the Moon from the point of view of auspiciousness. Mercury is also a natural benefic planet. However, the direction of its influence changes according to the planet with which it occurs. So somewhere there is a lack of his natural goodness. Then Jupiter and Venus are the only two auspicious planets left. Venus usually changes its zodiac within a month. That is, he gives all the good and bad results in a month. That is, the presence of Venus gives auspiciousness for small incidents. But Guru Maharaj stays in one zodiac for about 13 months. #astroguru   #astroguruma #guruparivartan | Aquarius Zodiac |</strong></p>
<p><strong>Also their vision has a lot to do with it. For all the other auspicious planets, the seventh is the only aspect. </strong>But Guru Maharaj has a total of three darshans named Pancham, Seventh and Navam.<strong> The important thing is that being a natural benefic planet, their vision is more important than the location. Actually their eyes are considered like nectar. In other words, Guru Maharaj has the power to stay in the zodiac for 13 months and also gives auspicious places to four places in the magazine. According to the cause and effect of the four places, very auspicious results are given to the natives. That is why the change in the form of Guru Maharaj or his zodiac sign is very important. Now this is going to be especially important. Because they are about to embark on a pleasant journey, a journey that has been negative for the past three years. In our language, Guru Maharaj has been walking on rocky roads for the last three years. Even though he himself is on a rocky path, he has given as many auspicious results as he can. However, since his visit was in a state of conflict, it naturally affected the general public. After entering his Pisces sign, he will now begin his journey on a good four-lane road. As a result, everyone will get their very auspicious results. In this way, Guru Maharaj is entering Pisces from Aquarius on 13th April. What will be the effect of this zodiac sign on Aquarius? Let us understand it now.</strong></p>
<p><strong>If you see from the point of view of Aquarius, then Guru Maharaj will come to your second place. Actually Guru Maharaj is not the planet of your zodiac. However Guru Maharaja&#8217;s position, his zodiac change is always very important for you. Because they are your Dhanesh and Benefesh. He is the lord of the second and eleventh house in Aquarius. The second place in the magazine is considered the place of wealth, the voice of the family. Therefore, we consider the eleventh house as the place of profit and fulfillment of desires. Considering the causality of these two places, very important things come under the jurisdiction of Guru Maharaj. Now they are going to enter your second place in their Pisces. Due to which this situation will be created in Dhanesh wealth. Which is considered very auspicious. You will get very auspicious results during this period. Your speech will attain enlightenment and spiritual level. When you create a topic, your study, your knowledge will show through that structure. People who are Aquarius born writers will be able to delve into their writing. Wisdom will be reflected in the voice of the speakers. | Aquarius Zodiac |</strong></p>
<p><strong>Overall, Guru Maharaja entering the second place will benefit you in many ways. More importantly, Guru Maharaja in second place will be able to complete the economic triangle in the magazine alone. Because Dhanasthan is one of the places of the triangle and Guru Maharaj who comes in any position of the triangle alone has the ability to complete the triangle. Also, since this is your Dhanesh and benesh, you will get a lot of benefits from this triangle. The magazine covers various yogas. Economic triangle is a very important and beneficial yoga. This yoga is formed by the sum of the third, sixth and tenth yogas. Now that Guru Maharaja will enter your second position, his vision will move to the sixth and tenth position. So this economic triangle is going to end here. This triangle is considered very important for monetization. Because earning money is the basic need of the world. One cannot deny that most other problems are easily solved with adequate income. Earning money is very important especially in today&#8217;s modern world. which you are going to get. #astroguru #guruparivartan</strong></p>
<p><strong> Another important factor is that your family may develop during this time. It can also be called auspicious effect. Of course, this increase can happen in different ways. A new child may be born in the family. Marriage of boy or girl. This method can also lead to the development of the family. In short, in the second place, Guru Maharaj will give you auspicious results and benefits along with earning money. You have to be more discriminatory in the support you provide to other people.</strong></p>
<p><strong>It is said that when good times begin, good things happen to us in many ways. The arrival of Guru Maharaj in the second place can be said to be the beginning of good times for you. Because Guru Maharaj is not going to give you money alone. Apart from this, they will be good for you in many other ways. He has a total of three ideas, the fifth, the seventh and the ninth. Their vision is more important than their position. Because his vision is called nectar vision. Accordingly, the fifth sight of Guru Maharaj will fall on your sixth position in the second place. From the sixth position in the magazine we look at health, job, debt, competitors, enemies. The result of Guru Maharaj&#8217;s auspicious vision at this place is stability in the job, creating opportunities for advancement, bringing forth one&#8217;s work in the field, changing the direction of work. Along with this, the right castes will also get promotion opportunities. Those who need loan can get it easily. Your opponents will not be able to do much harm to you. They will be more engaged in their work. Because the Cancer of the Moon comes in your sixth house. Jupiter and Moon are friendly planets. So from this point of view you will get more auspicious results.</strong></p>
<p><strong>After this, the seventh sight of Guru Maharaj will fall on your eighth place. Aquarius is a very intelligent creature. According to this, the effect of this vision is that if you are doing some intellectual work, doing research, if you are doing a deep study of a subject, then the chances of success in that work will increase greatly. Along with this, the possibility of family benefits and sudden gains will increase. Where you have already invested, there will be opportunities to make gains. Although the eighth position is considered negative in a nutshell, but by the grace of Guru Maharaj, you will get very auspicious results from this position as well. </strong></p>
<p><strong>After this the ninth sight of Guru Maharaj will fall on your tenth place. The tenth place in the magazine is called Karma Sthana. The sign of Mars in Scorpio appears here in Aquarius. Mars and Jupiter are friendly planets. Therefore, there will be special success in the treatment between Dhanesh and Dashmesh. The special thing is that whenever Mars comes in Pisces, Cancer, Scorpio, you will get a chance to make sudden profit this year. Because the tenth is your Karmesh. Guru Maharaj&#8217;s auspicious sight is falling on him in the tenth house and Mars clearly changes the zodiac in one and a half months. So Guru Maharaja stays in one zodiac for thirteen months. Therefore, whenever Mars comes in the sight of Guru Maharaj, you will get special benefits. More importantly, the direction of these benefits will be primarily financial. In short, Guru Maharaja, who comes in the place of wealth, is going to give you complete wealth. You should make full use of it. |  Kumbh Rashi</strong></p>
<p><strong>Talking about the remedies, astrology tells many small measures which anyone can do easily. There is no need to do anything special for this. Furthermore, even if the solution is small, the effect is huge. The only condition is that they should be corrected with full faith. According to this, keeping in mind the measures of Aquarius, the people of Aquarius should be given food in old age homes. Because Guru Maharaja is about to enter your second place. There, they will be in your voice. According to this, you should donate food to the old age home. This remedy will be very beneficial for you.</strong></p>
<p><strong>Thus, I think this information is sufficient to understand the effect of Jupiter change on Aquarius. So let&#8217;s stop here in today&#8217;s episode. In the next section, we will study the effects on the next zodiac sign. So let&#8217;s see you again in the next part. #astroguru #astroguruma #guruparivartan</strong></p>
<p><strong>Thank you!</strong></p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>Good luck! </strong></p>
<p> </p>
</div>


<p><strong>Other :  <a href="http://www.youtube.com/manomayjyotish">Youtube </a>: <a href="/home">Home </a>: <a href="/blog">Blogs </a>: <a href="/about-us">About us</a> : <a href="https://goo.gl/maps/qDSTBeUYcfeNwDkH7">Google Buisness </a></strong></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/jupiter-change-aquarius-rashi/">Jupiter Change &#8211; Kumbh Raas | Aquarius zodiac |</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Manomay Jyotish</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/jupiter-change-aquarius-rashi/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Guru change &#8211; Virgo Rasa &#8211; Daily Horoscope</title>
		<link>/guru-change-virgo-horoscope/</link>
					<comments>/guru-change-virgo-horoscope/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 05:30:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1091</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Guru change &#8211; Virgo Rasa &#8211; Daily Horoscope Virgo Zodiac &#124; Virgo Horoscope &#124;   Guru change &#8211; Virgo Rasa &#8211; Daily Horoscope  wish fulfillment with profit   Hello! I am Mrs.Sneha Mane warmly welcomes all the astrologers and People. Planets travel continuously. They enter from one zodiac sign to another through transits. They have &#8230;</p>
<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="/guru-change-virgo-horoscope/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Guru change &#8211; Virgo Rasa &#8211; Daily Horoscope</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/guru-change-virgo-horoscope/">Guru change &#8211; Virgo Rasa &#8211; Daily Horoscope</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Manomay Jyotish</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h1><strong>Guru change &#8211; Virgo Rasa &#8211; Daily Horoscope</strong></h1>



<p>Virgo Zodiac | Virgo Horoscope |</p>


<figure class="wp-block-post-featured-image"><img width="375" height="375" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Virgo-6.png" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Guru change &#8211; Virgo Rasa &#8211; Daily Horoscope" loading="lazy" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Virgo-6.png 375w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Virgo-6-300x300.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Virgo-6-150x150.png 150w" sizes="(max-width: 375px) 100vw, 375px" /></figure>

<p> </p>
<div>
<h1><strong>Guru change &#8211; Virgo Rasa &#8211; Daily Horoscope </strong></h1>
<p><strong>wish fulfillment with profit</strong></p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>Hello!</strong></p>
<p><strong>I am Mrs.Sneha Mane warmly welcomes all the astrologers and People. Planets travel continuously. They enter from one zodiac sign to another through transits. They have good or bad effect on human life. We are constantly analyzing these zodiac changes of the planets. Accordingly, all the planets are changing their zodiac signs in the coming April. In this, the change of zodiac sign of Guru Maharaj, who is called a natural benefic planet, will be auspicious for all the zodiac signs in many ways. Because they are entering your voice. Guru Maharaj&#8217;s zodiac will change on 13th April and we are analyzing their effects according to the zodiac. In today&#8217;s episode how can we change this Guru Maharaj&#8217;s zodiac sign for Virgo? We will discuss this in detail.</strong></p>
<p><strong>To understand this better, we have to first understand the information about Jupiter and its causation. Jupiter is the natural benefic planet or the most auspicious of all the planets. Therefore the success or failure of that caste or the life of that caste is determined by the position of the guru in the magazine. Another very important thing is that Guru Maharaj has the power to make four out of twelve places auspicious in the magazine. Because along with their position, their three visions also have a lot of influence. In fact, their vision is called nectar vision. Guru Maharaja is responsible for the end of life, education, marriage, redemption with children, which we can call death or salvation. The creation in the activities of such Guru Maharaja has decreased in the last three-four years. His journey started in a sad way. #astroguru  #astroguruma #guruparivartan</strong></p>
<p><strong>Of course, Ketu was also sitting with him when he first entered his Sagittarius sign. As a result, there was a meeting of Guru-Ketu. Actually, there was a planetary war between the two. In which Guru Maharaj was defeated. As a result, Guru Maharaj could not give his auspicious results in every way despite being in tune. Then Guru Maharaj entered Capricorn. Capricorn is their lowest form. After this he entered Aquarius at a very high speed. After that he again came in Capricorn and became debilitated. He again entered Aquarius. Even in the current situation, their journey has started from Aquarius. On 13th April 2022, he will again change his zodiac and enter Pisces. All the zodiac signs will get very auspicious results of their zodiac change. Of course some zodiac signs will get less and some zodiac signs will get more. But you will get good results, that&#8217;s for sure! Because Guru Maharaj is one of the most important natural benefic planets. Also, they stay in the same zodiac for a long time. Hence their influence has been brought to the fore by light. In this way, Guru Maharaj is entering Pisces from Aquarius on 13th April. What will be the effect of this zodiac sign on Virgo? Let us understand it now.</strong></p>
<p><strong>When you think of Kanya Raas or marriage, Guru Maharaja is the fourth and seventh house of your magazine. That is, he occupies two very important positions in the magazine, the fourth and the seventh. Therefore, even though Guru Maharaja may not be the karaka of your zodiac sign, his position, his appearance is very important to you. Now these zodiac signs are going to change and enter your seventh place. There he would form Hansa Yoga, one of the Panchmahapurush Yogas. Which is considered a very auspicious and important Raja Yoga. Therefore, virgins will get its extremely auspicious results. As you know, the seventh place in the magazine is considered to be the place of a married couple. Therefore, according to the factors of the place, your married life will be prosperous during this period. You will have proper communication with your spouse. We also see business from this location. Accordingly, your business will increase during this period. Your business will get a new direction. Which will pave the way for your progress.</strong></p>
<p><strong> Another important point is that Guru Maharaja, who enters the seventh place, will travel to three other important places at the same time through his vision. On the other hand, being the fourth lord, you will also get the auspicious results of that place. We all know that Guru Maharaj has a total of three darshans namely Pancham, Seventh and Navam. Their influence is also huge. In fact, their vision is more important than their condition. Because the vision of Guru Maharaj is called Amrit Drishti. Accordingly, Guru Maharaja&#8217;s fifth vision will fall from the seventh position to your eleventh position. The eleventh place in the magazine is known as the place of profit and fulfillment of desires. With the auspicious sight of Guru Maharaj at this place, all your wishes will be fulfilled suddenly. This will be the time for the fulfillment of all those secret desires that you have in your mind in the past. Along with this, you will also get the opportunity to take advantage of many ways. Castes will also benefit from this where they have invested earlier. In short, it will be a time of great profit and fulfillment of desires. You have to be more discriminatory in the support you provide to other people. More efforts should be made in this regard. So that this beneficial time can be put to good use.</strong></p>
<p><strong>After this, the seventh sight of Guru Maharaj will first fall on your zodiac sign. The caste has its own place in the first place in the magazine. From this point of view the personality is understood. Your personality will be enriched by the nectar of Guru Maharaj falling at this place. There will be many big and radical positive changes in your personality. The direction of your thoughts will be right. In fact, your thoughts or your personality as a whole will be much stronger. You have the art of presenting your subject, your point in the right way. That&#8217;s what you always do. But from the point of view of Guru Maharaj, their knowledge will increase. That is to say, a proper, careful layout will be done by you. As the knowledge increases, so does the chances of success for the learners. There will be a lot of progress in education, study, knowledge. In fact, if you say that all the sattvik qualities of Guru Maharaja will come to you, it doesn&#8217;t matter. You have to be more discriminatory in the support you provide to other people. #astroguru #astroguruma #guruparivartan</strong></p>
<p><strong>After this, the ninth sight of Guru Maharaj will fall on your third place. The third place in the magazine is known as the place of strength and diligence. Due to the auspicious sight of Guru Maharaj at this place, the direction of your labor will be right. Doing the right thing for the right reason and getting success out of it can be said to be your specialty in this age. In short, by the grace of Guru Maharaj, the direction of your hard work, your actions will be correct during this period. This will give you the right result. At the same time, brotherhood and small and big journeys are also seen from the third place. Accordingly, your brotherhood will increase. You are going to travel big and small. The special thing is that these trips will also be beneficial for you.</strong></p>
<p><strong>Overall, Guru Maharaja is the owner of two very important places in your magazine, the fourth and the seventh. Because of this both these places are going to be auspicious. Also, he will have auspicious sight in three places i.e. profit place, first place and third place. A total of five such places in your magazine will be auspicious at the same time. You will also get very auspicious results according to the reasons for those five places. For about thirteen months, Guru Maharaj will remain in Pisces, that is, you will be in the seventh position. That is, you will continue to get these auspicious results for thirteen months. Therefore, this visible girl child of Guru Maharaj will be very important for the caste.</strong></p>
<p><strong>On the other hand, on April 29, Shani Maharaj will also change his zodiac sign and enter your sixth place. They are the fifth lord and sixth lord of your zodiac. Therefore, your zodiac sign will also get very auspicious results. Actually, in this April, all the planets will change the zodiac. This is going to be a very big historical event in the world of astrology. The special thing is that most of the planets are going to be very auspicious for Virgo. So surely this time will be very important and beneficial for you. In fact, the results will remain the same throughout the year. Various opportunities for progress and advancement will arise for you. You too will be able to take advantage of this. In fact, you should take it. Because when the time is auspicious, our efforts should be increased in the real sense. Because the success rate is definitely higher.</strong></p>
<p><strong>Guru Maharaja will help you in achieving this. Although one of the auspicious Raja Yogas is being created by him in your magazine, one thing you should keep in mind here. That is, Jupiter is not a karaka planet for Virgo. As a result, centralized loopholes are arising here as well. Nevertheless, Guru Maharaj is known as the natural benefic planet or the most auspicious of all the planets. Therefore, even if defects arise, auspicious results are obtained from them. You have to be more discriminatory in the support you provide to other people. Guru Maharaj will surely give you its auspicious results.</strong></p>
<p><strong>Talking about the remedies, astrology tells many small measures which anyone can do easily. There is no need to do anything special for this. Furthermore, even if the solution is small, the effect is huge. The only condition is that they should be corrected with full faith. According to this, as mentioned earlier, considering the remedies for Virgo, Guru Maharaj is going to form Hans Yoga in the week of Virgo. Which is going to be very beneficial for you. During this, girls should serve the cow. Cow should be circumcised. Add green fodder. This remedy will be very beneficial for you.</strong></p>
<p><strong>Thus, I think this information is sufficient to understand the effect of Jupiter change on Virgo. So let&#8217;s stop here in today&#8217;s episode. In the next section, we will study the effects on the next zodiac sign. So let&#8217;s see you again in the next part. #astroguru  #astroguruma #guruparivartan</strong></p>
<p><strong>Thank you!</strong></p>
<p><strong>This  was Virgo Horoscope from April | Virgo Zodiac |</strong></p>
<p><strong>Good luck!</strong></p>
<p><strong>Other</strong> : <strong><a href="https://youtube.com/manomayjyotish/">Youtube</a> | <a href="/blog/">Blogs</a> | <a href="https://goo.gl/maps/ZkCBF2XYK3NxEUcQ8">Google Buisness</a> | <a href="/about-us">About us</a> | </strong></p>
<p> </p>
</div>
<p> </p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/guru-change-virgo-horoscope/">Guru change &#8211; Virgo Rasa &#8211; Daily Horoscope</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Manomay Jyotish</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/guru-change-virgo-horoscope/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Jupiter Change &#8211; Mithun Rasa  &#124; Guru Maharaj &#124; Gemini Zodiac &#124;</title>
		<link>/jupiter-change-mithun-rasa-gemini/</link>
					<comments>/jupiter-change-mithun-rasa-gemini/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sneha Mane]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 05:30:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gemini]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Zodiac]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1058</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>  Hello! Welcome to Manomay Jyotish &#124; Manomay Jyotish and Vadhuvar , Satara &#124; मनोमय ज्योतिष  &#124; Gemini I am Professor Mrs.Sneha Mane warmly welcomes all the astrologers . Today we are seeing Horoscope of Gemini Zodiac . The planets keep on moving continuously. They enter from one zodiac sign to another through transits. They &#8230;</p>
<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="/jupiter-change-mithun-rasa-gemini/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Jupiter Change &#8211; Mithun Rasa  &#124; Guru Maharaj &#124; Gemini Zodiac &#124;</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/jupiter-change-mithun-rasa-gemini/">Jupiter Change &#8211; Mithun Rasa  | Guru Maharaj | Gemini Zodiac |</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Manomay Jyotish</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<script async="async" data-cfasync="false" src="//pl17043992.effectivecpmcontent.com/5ceee80be7b404130111bed642010939/invoke.js"></script>
<div id="container-5ceee80be7b404130111bed642010939"></div>


<div>
<figure id="attachment_2956" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-2956" style="width: 408px" class="wp-caption alignnone"><a href="https://youtube.com/manomayjyotish" target="_blank" rel="noopener"><img loading="lazy" class="wp-image-2956" src="https://drjyotijoshi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/word-image-14.png" sizes="(max-width: 408px) 100vw, 408px" srcset="https://drjyotijoshi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/word-image-14.png 408w, https://drjyotijoshi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/word-image-14-300x300.png 300w, https://drjyotijoshi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/word-image-14-150x150.png 150w, https://drjyotijoshi.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/word-image-14-100x100.png 100w" alt="Gemini | Guru | Jupiter | Astroguru " width="408" height="408" /></a><figcaption id="caption-attachment-2956" class="wp-caption-text"><strong>Gemini | Guru | Jupiter | Astroguru | Horoscope | Rashifal</strong></figcaption></figure>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>Hello! Welcome to Manomay Jyotish | Manomay Jyotish and Vadhuvar , Satara | मनोमय ज्योतिष  | Gemini</strong></p>
<p><strong>I am Professor Mrs.Sneha Mane warmly welcomes all the astrologers . Today we are seeing Horoscope of Gemini Zodiac . The planets keep on moving continuously. They enter from one zodiac sign to another through transits. They have good or bad effect on human life. We are constantly analyzing these zodiac changes of the planets. Accordingly, in the coming April, all the planets are changing their zodiac signs. In this, the change of zodiac sign of Guru Maharaj, who is called a natural benefic planet, will be auspicious for all the zodiac signs in many ways. Because they are entering your voice. Guru Maharaj&#8217;s zodiac will change on 13th April and we are analyzing their effects according to the zodiac. In today&#8217;s episode how can we change this zodiac sign of Guru Maharaj for Gemini? We will discuss this in detail. #rashifal Rashifal </strong></p>
<p><strong>To understand this better, we have to first understand the information about Jupiter and its causation. Of all the planets, Moon, Mercury, Jupiter and Venus are the four natural benefic planets. However, the condition applies to the moon that the moon near the full moon is considered auspicious and the moon near the new moon is considered inauspicious. The farther the Moon is from the Sun, the further away it is from the houses. Apart from this, many conditions apply to the Moon from the point of view of auspiciousness. Mercury is also a natural benefic planet. However, the direction of its influence changes according to the planet with which it occurs. So somewhere there is a lack of his natural goodness. Then Jupiter and Venus are the only two auspicious planets left. Venus usually changes its zodiac within a month. That is, he gives all the good and bad results in a month. That is, the presence of Venus gives auspiciousness for small incidents. But Guru Maharaj stays in one zodiac for about 13 months. #Rashifal Rashifal</strong></p>
<p><strong>Also their vision has a lot to do with it. For all the other auspicious planets, the seventh is the only aspect. But Guru Maharaj has a total of three darshans named Pancham, Seventh and Navam. The important thing is that being a natural benefic planet, their vision is more important than the location. Actually their eyes are considered like nectar. In other words, Guru Maharaj has the power to stay in the zodiac for 13 months and also keep four places in the magazine in an auspicious way. According to the cause and effect of those four places, very auspicious results are given to the natives. That is why the change in the form of Guru Maharaj or his zodiac sign is very important. Now this is going to be especially important. Because since last three years of continuous negative, struggling journey, now they are going to start a pleasant journey. In our language, Guru Maharaj has been walking on rocky roads for the last three years. Even though he himself is on a rocky path, he has given as many auspicious results as he can. However, since his journey was in a state of conflict, it naturally affected the general public. Having entered their own Pisces, they will now begin their journey on a fine four-lane road. As a result, everyone will get their very auspicious results. In this way, Guru Maharaj is entering Pisces from Aquarius on 13th April. What will be the effect of this zodiac change on Gemini? Let us understand it now.</strong></p>
</div>


<script type="text/javascript">
	atOptions = {
		'key' : '3cc6993eb736f2fc864720745cf30f23',
		'format' : 'iframe',
		'height' : 60,
		'width' : 468,
		'params' : {}
	};
	document.write('<scr' + 'ipt type="text/javascript" src="http' + (location.protocol === 'https:' ? 's' : '') + '://www.highconvertingformats.com/3cc6993eb736f2fc864720745cf30f23/invoke.js"></scr' + 'ipt>');
</script>



<p><strong>When you think of Gemini, Guru Maharaj is the seventh lord and tenth lord of your zodiac. In other words, Guru Maharaja is the lord of Mithun or the two most important centers of marriage, the seventh and the tenth. That&#8217;s why Guru Maharaj is a very important planet for you and hence his zodiac sign is very important for you. For the past few months this has been your fate. Now these zodiac signs are going to change and enter your tenth place. In fact, Jupiter is not the significator of Gemini. Because he is the master of the two center places, he is to blame. Even so, owning one is still out of reach for the average person. Especially Guru Maharaja gets the responsibility of marital happiness, matrimonial partner, business, karma. In this way, Guru Maharaj will now enter your tenth place by changing the zodiac. Pisces is their source of water. Their position can be said to be very auspicious for Gemini natives.</strong></p>



<p><strong>The most important feature of Guru Maharaja in the tenth place is that there he will form Hansa Yoga which is one of the Panch Mahapurush Yoga. The most important thing is that this Raja Yoga is going to be formed at your place of Karma. When we think about the Kendra position, according to astrological laws, the fourth position is stronger than the first position. The seventh is considered to be the strongest position and the tenth is considered to be the strongest centre. One of the most auspicious planets in such a powerful center, Guru Maharaja and the Panchmahapurush Yoga created by him, Raja Yoga is one of the most important. Now Guru Maharaj will stay at your place of work for about thirteen months. This whole period will be very useful for starting your business, business security, business development, new business. This New Year will be especially beneficial for the people of Gemini zodiac who work in the field of education, writers and poets, those working in the field of management, new work in the field of education, studying in the field of education. . Research. #astroguru&nbsp; #guruparivartan #astrologer #horoscope</strong></p>



<html><script type="text/javascript">
	atOptions = {
		'key' : 'c202934202ba8ec5280eda3242cc0c9c',
		'format' : 'iframe',
		'height' : 50,
		'width' : 320,
		'params' : {}
	};
	document.write('<scr' + 'ipt type="text/javascript" src="http' + (location.protocol === 'https:' ? 's' : '') + '://www.highconvertingformats.com/c202934202ba8ec5280eda3242cc0c9c/invoke.js"></scr' + 'ipt>');
</script></html>



<p><strong>&nbsp;Guru Maharaj entering your tenth position will make your tenth position auspicious. At the same time, their vision will have a very good effect on you. We all know that Guru Maharaja has a total of three darshans namely Pancham, Seventh and Navam. The special thing is that their ideas are given more importance than places. Because their vision is considered to be nectar. Accordingly, the fifth vision of Guru Maharaj will fall in your second position in the tenth position. Then the seventh vision will come to the fourth position and the ninth vision will come to the sixth position. The second place in the magazine is called the place of wealth, family and speech. When Guru Maharaj&#8217;s nectar falls at this place, knowledge will flow through your speech. Which means it&#8217;s also going to be the most confusing time of the year. There will be money too. Because the second place is also the place of wealth. There are many ways in which you can earn money. Wealth will be created through karma, especially from your business. There will also be family happiness of the partner.</strong></p>



<p><strong>After this, the seventh sight of Guru Maharaj will fall on your fourth place. The fourth place in the magazine is called the place of happiness. From this various things like Vastu, Vehicle, Land, Happiness, Motherhood are seen. With the auspicious sight of Guru Maharaj at this place, there will be further increase in happiness, peace and prosperity in your home. Apart from this, very auspicious Vastu Yoga, Vehicle Yoga will also be formed for you. Therefore, the people of Gemini who have been dreaming of Vastu or Vehicle for many days, their dream will come true during this period. Those things will also be beneficial for you. Because that auspicious Yoga Guru Maharaj is going to create for you. The important thing is that during this time your Bhagya Shani Maharaj will also enter your destiny. A planet like Rahu will be in your benefic position and Guru Maharaj will be in your tenth position. Gemini sign people will get a lot of support from these three. Therefore, after the coming April month, Gemini native will make great progress in many areas, on many fronts. Of course, progress alone is not enough. If there is no happiness, prosperity, unity, love in your house, then money is useless. But during this time happiness, peace and love will be created in your house. There will be family happiness and wealth.</strong></p>



<p><strong>After this, the ninth sight of Guru Maharaj will fall on your sixth place. Health, job, debt, competitors, enemies are seen from the sixth position in the magazine. The result of having auspicious sight of Guru Maharaj at this place is that your enemies will automatically retreat or they will not have much enthusiasm in opposing you. Those who need loan can get it easily. It can also be beneficial for you. That is, it will be used for the same purpose for which you have taken it. The most important thing is that you will get good health during this period.</strong></p>



<p><strong>In short, Guru Maharaja, the creator of Hansa Yoga, will give you auspicious results in all directions. Enjoy it to the fullest. Actually, from now on there are going to be big changes in your life which are very positive, auspicious and beneficial. You should make full use of it. Live life to the fullest. Earn money the right way. Take proper care of your family and live a good life.</strong></p>



<p><strong>Talking about the remedies, astrology tells many small measures which can be easily done by anyone. There is no need to do anything special for this. Furthermore, even if the solution is small, the effect is huge. The only condition is that they should be dealt with with full confidence. According to this, considering the measures of Gemini, as it has been told earlier that Guru Maharaj is going to create Hans Yoga from the tenth position in your magazine. Therefore, the people of Gemini zodiac should help a young man in his business. Then you can guide him or help him. In short, he should cooperate for the prosperity of his business without any intention. Which will benefit you too.</strong></p>



<p><strong>Thus, I think this information is sufficient to understand the effect of Jupiter change on Gemini. So let&#8217;s stop here in today&#8217;s episode. In the next section we will study the effects on the next zodiac sign. So let&#8217;s see you in the next part. #astroguru&nbsp; &nbsp;#guruparivartan</strong></p>



<p><strong>Thank you!</strong></p>



<p><strong>Good luck!</strong></p>



<p><strong>Jyotish Pandit Mrs.Sneha Mane</strong></p>



<p><strong>More : <a href="/about-us/">About US</a> :&nbsp; <a href="https://youtube.com/manomayjyotish">Youtube </a>:&nbsp; <a href="/blog/">Blogs</a></strong></p>



<script type="text/javascript">
	atOptions = {
		'key' : 'e1a3efc8baee9f75248b8f0cb6c088bc',
		'format' : 'iframe',
		'height' : 300,
		'width' : 160,
		'params' : {}
	};
	document.write('<scr' + 'ipt type="text/javascript" src="http' + (location.protocol === 'https:' ? 's' : '') + '://www.highconvertingformats.com/e1a3efc8baee9f75248b8f0cb6c088bc/invoke.js"></scr' + 'ipt>');
</script>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/jupiter-change-mithun-rasa-gemini/">Jupiter Change &#8211; Mithun Rasa  | Guru Maharaj | Gemini Zodiac |</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Manomay Jyotish</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/jupiter-change-mithun-rasa-gemini/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>प्रेमाची कथाप्रेम ही एक निसर्गाने दिलेली देणगी आहे &#124; प्रेम &#124; love &#124; Love story &#124; प्रेम</title>
		<link>/story-marathi-love/</link>
					<comments>/story-marathi-love/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sneha Mane]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 03:18:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1042</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>प्रेमाची कथाप्रेम ही एक निसर्गाने दिलेली देणगी आहे. समाजामध्ये सर्व लोकांमध्ये आपापला मध्ये स्नेह, प्रेम, जिव्हाळा, सहकार्य असले की व्यक्ती मधील प्रेम टिकून राहते. नुकत्याच वयात आलेल्या तरुण-तरुणी मधील आवडता विषय म्हणजे प्रेम.उर्मिला तिच्या बाबतीत हे घडत होते. तीही कोणाच्यातरी प्रेमात पडली होती. मयूर हे तिच्यावर प्रेम करीत होता. हे प्रेम भावना दोघांच्या मनात खेळत &#8230;</p>
<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="/story-marathi-love/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">प्रेमाची कथाप्रेम ही एक निसर्गाने दिलेली देणगी आहे &#124; प्रेम &#124; love &#124; Love story &#124; प्रेम</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/story-marathi-love/">प्रेमाची कथाप्रेम ही एक निसर्गाने दिलेली देणगी आहे | प्रेम | love | Love story | प्रेम</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Manomay Jyotish</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>प्रेमाची कथाप्रेम ही एक निसर्गाने दिलेली देणगी आहे. समाजामध्ये सर्व लोकांमध्ये आपापला मध्ये स्नेह, प्रेम, जिव्हाळा, सहकार्य असले की व्यक्ती मधील प्रेम टिकून राहते. नुकत्याच वयात आलेल्या तरुण-तरुणी मधील आवडता विषय म्हणजे प्रेम.उर्मिला तिच्या बाबतीत हे घडत होते. तीही कोणाच्यातरी प्रेमात पडली होती. मयूर हे तिच्यावर प्रेम करीत होता. हे प्रेम भावना दोघांच्या मनात खेळत होती. परंतु याबाबतीत कोणालाच काहीच माहीत नव्हते.तसे बघायला गेले तर उर्मिलालाचे नुकतेच आईचे छत्र हरवले होते. त्यामुळे ती तिच्या मावशीकडे आली होती. मावशीच्या गावातील कॉलेजच्या तिसऱ्या वर्षाला  शिक्षण घेत होती. गेली दोन वर्षे ती प्रेमात बुडालेली होती. आता तिच्या लग्नाची जबाबदारी तिच्या मावशीकडे होती. ती तिच्या लग्नाचा विचार करत होती. ती तिच्यासाठी गावोगावी स्थळे पाहत होती.उर्मिला तिच्या प्रेमाची हाकीकत मावशीला किती सांगायचे याचा विचारत होती. गावी असलेले वडिलांनाही तिला सांगायचे होते.मयूरव उर्मिला  याबद्दल विचार करत होते. त्यावेळी त्यांना प्रश्न पडला की आपलं प्रेम होईल का?लग्नात दोन्ही घरची लोकं परवानगी देतील का? गावाकडची लोक काय म्हणतील? लग्न करण्यास कोण बाधा आणेल. असे नाना प्रकारचे प्रश्न सतत मनात घोळत होते. हे बाजू तिच्या मैत्रिणीना सांगत असताना. एका मैत्रिणीने तिला एस्ट्रोलॉजी कन्सल्टिंग असे सुचवले.त्यावेळी तीला मनोमय ज्योतिष केंद्र संचलित. ज्योतिष पंडित स्नेहा माने यांच्याकडे आली त्यांच्याकडून तिने वैयक्तिक मार्गदर्शन घेतले.समुपदेशन करताना तिने सुरुवातीला तिची सर्व हकीकत सांगितली. नुकतीच शेवटच्या वर्षाची परीक्षा दिली आहे. आई नसल्यामुळे मावशी कडे राहते मावशी सांभाळ करते. त्यामुळे मावशींनी तिच्या लग्नाची पूर्ण जबाबदारी उचलली होती. परंतु तिच्या मावशीच्या गावातील एक मयूर नावाचा तरुण आवडत होता. तोही एकटाच आई वडिलांचे छत्र हरवले होते. आजी आजोबा बरोबर राहत होता. शेती करत एका ठिकाणी नोकरी करत होता. त्यांचा असा प्रश्न होता की आमचे प्रेम आहे पण बाहेर सांगायला भीती वाटते घरातील लोकं कशी प्रतिक्रिया देतील. त्यांनी जर हे आमचे नाते नाकारले तर कसे होईल?दोघांच्या पत्रिका पाहिल्यावरअसे आढळून आले की मुलीच्या पत्रिकेमध्ये शुक्र हा बलवान स्थितीत होता. मी प्रेम विवाहाचे योग बोलके होते. त्याप्रमाणे पत्रिके वरून दोघांचे स्वभाव पाहिले. उर्मिला तशी स्थिर, धीमी, विचारी, मनाचा तोल जाऊन देणारी, शांतपणे काम करणारी, कोणत्याही बदलास व परिस्थितीस सामोरे जाणारी, वरून जरी ती प्रत्यक्ष रागिट वाटली तर मन प्रेमळ आहे. धाडसी पण थोडी अहंकारी आहे.नेहमी गुप्त राहणारी लपवणारी अशा स्वभावाचा असल्याने, आपल्या मनाचा थांगपत्ता लागू देत नाही. जरा काही मनाविरुद्ध झाले की लगेच राग व्यक्त करणे व स्पष्ट बोलक्या मनाची आहे. मयूरची ही पत्रिका पाहिली. चंचल ,प्रेमळ, दयाळू, प्रेमाचा भुकेला, संवेदनशील, नेहमी स्वप्नात रंगणारा, मनमोकळे आणि पारदर्शक आणि जेणेकरून जीवनात सुख व आनंद निर्माण करण्यात तरबेज होता. मोठ्या मनाचा, कुटुंबावर खूप प्रेम करायचा, त्याच्या आईवर ही खुप प्रेम करायचा. मित्र परिवारही मोठा होता. असा सात्विक, सदाचारी नेहमी दुसऱ्याच्या हिताचा विचार करणारा अशामुळे इकडे समाजशील, सहनशीलता होती.त्यांचा पुढचा प्रश्न होता की आमचा प्रेमविवाह योग आहे का?कुंडलीत असे दिसत होते की, समाजाचा विरोध असला तरी, मित्र जीवापाड मदत करत होती. मित्र-मैत्रिणीची मदत मिळेल. दोघांचेही लाभेश बलवान होते.गावातील बहुतेक व्यक्तींना समजले. मयूर च्या घरातील व्यक्तींनी सहमत दाखवली. उर्मिला च्या मावशी काकांनी यावर विचार केला. आणि तिच्या वडिलांना बोलावून यावर चर्चा केली. अखेरीस लग्नाला होकार मिळाला. आणि त्यांचा विवाह यशस्वी झाला. याचे कारण कुंडलीतील शुक्राची स्थिती उत्तम होती. परंतु जोडण्यासाठी राहू-केतू ची बाधा येत होती. त्या पद्धतीने राहू-केतू ची उपासना वाढवली. व मनापासून उपाय केले.</strong></p>



<p>Other : <strong><a href="http://www.manomayjyotish.com/">Home</a></strong> : <strong><a href="http://www.manomayjyotish.com/about-us">About Us</a></strong> : <a href="http://www.manomayjyotish.com/blog" rel="nofollow"><strong>Blogs</strong></a> : <strong><a href="http://www.youtube.com/c/manomayjyotish">YouTube</a></strong> </p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img alt="" /></figure>


<figure class="wp-block-post-featured-image"><img width="728" height="410" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/wD8na2.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="प्रेमाची कथाप्रेम ही एक निसर्गाने दिलेली देणगी आहे | प्रेम | love | Love story | प्रेम" loading="lazy" /></figure><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/story-marathi-love/">प्रेमाची कथाप्रेम ही एक निसर्गाने दिलेली देणगी आहे | प्रेम | love | Love story | प्रेम</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Manomay Jyotish</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/story-marathi-love/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rahu-Ketu change &#8211; Tul Rasa</title>
		<link>/rahu-ketu-change-tul-rasa/</link>
					<comments>/rahu-ketu-change-tul-rasa/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 12:29:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Astrology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jyotish]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ketu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[planetary zodiac]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rahu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rahu and Ketu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Saturn]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Todays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Todays Horoscope]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1031</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>  Rahu Rahu-Ketu inauspiciousness will reduce the intensity of saturn Hello!   We always analyze the planetary zodiac changes and their effects from time to time. Accordingly, we are studying two planets J Rahu and Ketu which will change in the coming April month on 12th April. Rahu will enter Aries from Taurus and Ketu &#8230;</p>
<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="/rahu-ketu-change-tul-rasa/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Rahu-Ketu change &#8211; Tul Rasa</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rahu-ketu-change-tul-rasa/">Rahu-Ketu change &#8211; Tul Rasa</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Manomay Jyotish</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p> </p>
<div>
<h3><strong>Rahu</strong></h3>
<p><strong>Rahu-Ketu inauspiciousness</strong></p>
<p><strong>will reduce the intensity of saturn</strong></p>
<p><strong>Hello!</strong></p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>We always analyze the planetary zodiac changes and their effects from time to time. Accordingly, we are studying two planets J Rahu and Ketu which will change in the coming April month on 12th April. Rahu will enter Aries from Taurus and Ketu will enter Libra from Scorpio. What effect will they actually have? We are studying it according to the zodiac. What will be the effect of this change on Libra today? We will understand this in detail. #rahuketuparivartan</strong></p>
<p><strong>To understand the importance of Rahu and Ketu&#8217;s change of zodiac, we have to first understand the information of these two planets. Suppose Venus is a planet along with Rahu in a native&#8217;s journal, then it will work to create ownership in the mind of the native. How should my partner be? How smart must that be? Should he be tactful or should he talk to others or not? The planet representing all these things is Rahu. Ketu has opposite mindset. This will work even if the spouse is pregnant. It will work no matter what. A person with no color combination can also love someone. Because in the caste of such castes there is a combination of Ketu and Venus. The special thing is that the world of such castes is also very good. Because Ketu does not care about these things.</strong></p>
<p><strong>Although the planets Rahu and Ketu are related to each other, they are both at different ends. Therefore, their effect is also opposite to each other. We can call Rahu the misery of Kaal. This is a shadow planet. He has a tendency to take revenge. It is also believed to be the cause of alcoholism and other bad habits. Accidents, theft, accidents, dacoity, displacement are all considered factors. But this does not completely spoil Rahu. He has some good stuff too. Rahu means to achieve something by working hard. Rahu means getting something quickly, enjoying material pleasures to the fullest. Therefore, in today&#8217;s 21st century, Rahu is of great importance in today&#8217;s modern era.</strong></p>
<p><strong>The planet Ketu has the opposite effect. It is the planet of liberation. Ketu is doing the work of taking man on the path of spirituality. If Ketu is strong in the horoscope of a person, then that person gets away from all the temptations of life. He is different than all. The causative planet of spirituality is actually three. These three planets are Saturn, Jupiter and Ketu. But there is a fundamental difference between these three. That is, Shani Maharaj tells the caste to behave with morality, justice and go towards salvation. Guru Maharaj tells Jataka that first complete all the actions, all the obligations and move towards salvation. So Ketu tells Jataka to renounce everything and move towards salvation. Of course Ketu is a planet that somewhere denies responsibility, we can say. Its effects are terrifying. Where he sits in the magazine, he works to create distance in the relationship. He is trying to destroy the causality of the planet he is sitting with. It also makes a distinction between the position in which it is sighted. Man gets bored because of the planet Ketu. So Rahu and Ketu&#8217;s zodiac sign is happening on 12th April. Rahu will enter Taurus from Aries and Ketu will enter Libra from Scorpio. What will be the effect of this change on Libra? Let us understand it now. </strong></p>
<p><strong> Looking at Libra, the arrival of Rahu will be in your seventh place. Also Ketu will arrive in your zodiac. Because these two planets change zodiac at the same time. Both start their journey at 180 degrees from each other and with rotational motion. Actually, these two planets are not points and their journey starts from a curved path. The impact of this visit is huge. Because both these planets are sitting firmly in the same zodiac for one and a half years. That is, Rahu and Ketu are the longest-lasting planets after Saturn in a zodiac. So this Rahu is in your seventh and Ketu is in your zodiac. They are showing a different kind of struggle in your life. I will also tell you the results of this struggle. However, Tul caste people should not be afraid of this. Because during this time Shani Maharaj is going to help you a lot. Therefore it is necessary to consider not only the fruits of Rahu-Ketu but also the auspicious results of Shani Maharaj or even Guru Maharaj. We will tell you that separately according to the amount.</strong></p>
<p><strong>Looking at the effect of Rahu, Rahu situated in the seventh house works to increase the ego of the partner somewhere. Takes your partner away from you or creates hatred between the two. At the same time, he loses family health. disturbs the peace of the family. So you have to take proper care of it. The world has said that a vessel must contain a vessel. However, it will be very important for you to take care that no controversy should arise. As you know Rahu has total three aspects: fifth, seventh and ninth. That is, he is seated at one place and his vision falling at three places is affected by the position of Rahu at four places. Accordingly, the fifth aspect of Rahu in the seventh position will move to the eleventh position. The eleventh place in the magazine is known as the place of profit and fulfillment of desires. After that the seventh sight will fall on your zodiac sign which is the first place and the ninth sight will fall on the third place which means strength and hard work. From the point of view of Rahu, being in the position of wish fulfillment from the seventh house, Rahu acts to not let your wishes come true or give everything other than what you want. Because their role is mainly in the case of non-fulfillment of their wishes.</strong></p>
<p><strong>The sight falling on Rahu&#8217;s zodiac will increase anger in your mind. At the same time, frustration can also increase. Because Ketu is also sitting there. The planet Ketu is the cause of depression. Your role will be to ignore a question or remain silent on something. You will have to face a lot of difficulties for this role. Because when we are constantly persecuted, wronged, harassed or harassed by our relatives, we are constantly thinking in our mind. In fact, it&#8217;s completely out of mind. Then somewhere its efficiency decreases. This could happen to you. Because in the week, the sight of Rahu will also fall at the place of your labor. From there he will work to remove your shortcomings. But even if all this is true, then the most important thing is that on April 29, Shani Maharaj will change your zodiac and enter your fifth place. From there his third vision will fall on Rahu. Saturn and Rahu are friendly planets. Also, Shani Maharaj is the Raja Yogakaraka planet of your magazine. Therefore Shani Maharaj will work to reduce the intensity of all the ill effects of Rahu that I have just told you. So it won&#8217;t bother you much. #bestastrologerinmaharashtra</strong></p>
<p><strong>In case of Ketu change, the coming of Ketu in your zodiac will work to change your thinking. This will constantly fill your mind with negative thoughts. All the bad things that are happening in the world are happening with me, this feeling will be formed in your mind. Whenever this feeling arises in your mind, I am giving you a suggestion that you should remember the dialogue between Karna and Lord Krishna at such a time. Which I also mentioned in some videos at that time. In this, Karna says, &#8220;Why all this happened to me? I was born and abandoned by my mother. what&#8217;s wrong with me? With this he presented all the miseries of life in front of Lord Krishna. Then Lord Krishna says to him, &#8220;You are telling this to a person who was planned to kill before birth. He was taken away from his mother as soon as he was born.&#8221; This is how Lord Krishna tries to calm his mind by telling him everything.</strong></p>
<p><strong>Accordingly, &#8216;Why in my case?&#8217; When you say so, you really have no right to say it. Because at that time many other auspicious works were done only in your case. Therefore Tul castes are specially advised to control their mind. Ketu coming to the zodiac and marriage place will try to take you away from you. Will try to create disappointment in the mind. In such an adverse situation, you have to overcome all these things of your own free will and move towards progress. Shani Maharaj will definitely help you in this work.  Overall even though it may have a negative effect on Tul castes but with the help of Shani Maharaj you are going to have a successful journey.</strong></p>
<p><strong>I think this information is sufficient to understand the effect of Rahu-Ketu change on Libra. So let&#8217;s stop here in today&#8217;s episode. In the next section, we will study the effects on the next zodiac sign. So let&#8217;s see you again in the next part.</strong></p>
<p><strong>Thank you!</strong></p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>Good luck!</strong></p>
<p><strong>Visit More : <a href="https://www.manomayjyotish.com/blog/">Blogs</a> | <a href="http://www.manomayjyotish.com/about-us/">About Us</a> | <a href="http://m.youtube.com/c/manomayjyotish/">Youtube</a></strong></p>
</div>

<figure class="wp-block-post-featured-image"><img width="428" height="338" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Rahu-And-Ketu-Images.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Rahu-Ketu change &#8211; Tul Rasa" loading="lazy" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Rahu-And-Ketu-Images.jpg 428w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Rahu-And-Ketu-Images-300x237.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 428px) 100vw, 428px" /></figure><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rahu-ketu-change-tul-rasa/">Rahu-Ketu change &#8211; Tul Rasa</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Manomay Jyotish</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/rahu-ketu-change-tul-rasa/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>अपनी प्रेमिका को खुश रखने का मंत्र &#124; Love &#124; Love Story &#124; Prem &#124; quotes &#124;  quotes in english &#124; Real Love &#124; Real Love Story &#124; real lover</title>
		<link>/prem-hindi-real-love/</link>
					<comments>/prem-hindi-real-love/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sneha Mane]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 09:50:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horoscope]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[love]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[love images]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[love quotes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[love quotes in english]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[love shayari in hindi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[love story]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[love wallpaper]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lover]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Quotes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rashi]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1018</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Real Love &#124; Real Love Story &#124; real love quotes &#124; Love &#124; मेष राशि Real Love &#124; Real Love Story &#124; real love quotes &#124; Love &#124; , यदि आपके प्रेमी या प्रेमिका की मेष राशि है, तो आपको एक ऐसा व्यक्ति मिला है जो जिद्दी, निडर, मजबूत, साहसी, तेज, महत्वपूर्ण है। आपका प्रिय &#8230;</p>
<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="/prem-hindi-real-love/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">अपनी प्रेमिका को खुश रखने का मंत्र &#124; Love &#124; Love Story &#124; Prem &#124; quotes &#124;  quotes in english &#124; Real Love &#124; Real Love Story &#124; real lover</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/prem-hindi-real-love/">अपनी प्रेमिका को खुश रखने का मंत्र | Love | Love Story | Prem | quotes |  quotes in english | Real Love | Real Love Story | real lover</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Manomay Jyotish</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h4 class="has-text-align-center wp-block-post-title">अपनी प्रेमिका को खुश रखने का मंत्र | Love | Love Story | Prem | quotes |  quotes in english | Real Love | Real Love Story | real lover</h4>

<figure class="wp-block-post-featured-image"><a href="/prem-hindi-real-love/"><img width="684" height="393" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/love.png" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="अपनी प्रेमिका को खुश रखने का मंत्र | Love | Love Story | Prem | quotes |  quotes in english | Real Love | Real Love Story | real lover" loading="lazy" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/love.png 684w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/02/love-300x172.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/02/love-600x345.png 600w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/02/love-150x86.png 150w" sizes="(max-width: 684px) 100vw, 684px" /></a></figure>


<h3 class="has-text-align-center has-large-font-size"> Real Love | Real Love Story | real love quotes | Love |</h3>



<h3 class="has-text-align-center"><strong>मेष राशि</strong></h3>



<p class="has-medium-font-size"><strong>Real Love | Real Love Story | real love quotes | Love | , यदि आपके प्रेमी या प्रेमिका की मेष राशि है, तो आपको एक ऐसा व्यक्ति मिला है जो जिद्दी, निडर, मजबूत, साहसी, तेज, महत्वपूर्ण है। आपका प्रिय कोई अजनबी नहीं बल्कि तूफान है। इसे ध्यान में रखते हुए, उन्हें समझना कठिन है, आपके लिए जीवन बदलने वाला साथी खोजना कठिन है, क्योंकि आप मुखर, मुखर हैं, भले ही थोड़ा कड़वा हो, आपको यह जानकर खुशी होगी कि उनका प्यार सच्चा है।</strong></p>



<h3 class="has-text-align-center"><strong>वृषभ</strong></h3>



<p class="has-medium-font-size"><br><strong>यदि आपका प्रेमी या प्रेमिका वृष राशि से है तो आपका प्रेमी या प्रेमिका वृष राशि से है।यह उनका सपना है, उनका मन प्यार में डूबा हुआ है, उनके चारों ओर निरंतर प्रेम का विचार लिपटा हुआ है, ऐसा प्रेमी या प्रेमी सुंदरता से प्यार करता है। उनके कला कौशल के साथ उनकी मदद करें, उनकी मदद करें, जानेमन या प्रेमी किसी की तारीफ करने के लिए पीछे मुड़कर न देखें, वे हमेशा तारीफ, तारीफ, तारीफ, तारीफ, तारीफ, तारीफ, तारीफ, तारीफ, तारीफ, तारीफ, तारीफ करना भी पसंद करते हैं। तारीफ, तारीफ तारो ताही के प्रेमी जैसा खुशमिजाज व्यक्ति मिलना आपकी नियति है या एक प्यार भरा स्पर्श ही काफी है।</strong></p>



<h3 class="has-text-align-center"><strong>मिथुन राशि</strong></h3>



<p class="has-medium-font-size"><br><strong>अगर आपका प्रेमी या प्रेमिका मिथुन है तो खुश रहें अगर आपका प्रेमी या प्रेमिका मिथुन है तो आपको यह स्वीकार करना होगा कि आप हमेशा खुश और उत्साहित रहते हैं क्योंकि आपका प्रिय बहुत सुंदर है, ये लोग हमेशा आपके बारे में सोचते हैं। वे गलतियाँ करते हैं क्योंकि उनके पास बहुत अच्छा कौशल है, मीठी बात करने वालों से सीखते हैं, बहुत प्यारे और शरारती होते हैं, लगातार दूसरों का दिल जीतते हैं, मिथुन प्रेमी अपने साथी को खुश रखने के तरीके सोचते हैं, और धम्मल एक मजेदार मजाक है। ऐसा माहौल, इसलिए यदि आपका प्रिय व्यक्ति मिथुन राशि में है, तो हमेशा चैट करें और मज़े करें!</strong></p>



<h3 class="has-text-align-center"><strong>कैंसर</strong></h3>



<p class="has-medium-font-size"><br><strong>प्यार का भूखा इंसान प्यार का भूखा होता है। कर्क राशि वाले बहुत प्यार करने वाले, दयालु, भावुक, स्नेही, भावुक, प्यार में बहने वाले होते हैं। ये प्रेमी प्यार के लिए उत्सुक होते हैं। अगर ऐसा प्यार भरा रवैया साथ दिया जाए, तो सुख आकाश में मावेनसा बन जाता है।कर्क राशि वाले खुले विचारों वाले और पारदर्शी होते हैं, पानी की तरह, दूसरों के जीवन में खुशियाँ और आनंद पैदा करते हैं, लोगों को सुखी जीवन जीने की कला देते हैं, बड़े दिल वाले बेहद संवेदनशील सुखी परोपकारी होते हैं, साथ देते हैं तो खुश रहते हैं।</strong></p>



<h3 class="has-text-align-center"><strong>सिंह </strong></h3>



<p class="has-medium-font-size"><br><strong>यदि कोई प्रिय सिंह हो तो तेजतर्रार व्यक्तित्व वाला सिंह होता है, हर अदा राजा के समान होता है मानो मोदेन एक सिद्धांत है जो झुकता नहीं है, अपमान में भी, ये लोग थाली हैं। !</strong></p>



<h3 class="has-text-align-center"><strong>कन्या</strong></h3>



<p class="has-medium-font-size"><br><strong>यदि आप कन्या राशि में हैं तो अपने प्रियजन को कैसे खुश रखें कन्या राशि वाले हमेशा अपने साथी को लेकर चिंतित रहते हैं। वे सोचते हैं कि वे क्या नहीं चाहते हैं, उनके हित हमेशा शीर्ष पर हैं, उनका प्यार कभी विफल नहीं होता है, बहुत प्यार और कोमल दिल वाले व्यक्ति को ढूंढना मुश्किल है! आपके साथी कितनी भी गलतियाँ करें, ये लोग आपको उनकी दया, क्षमा और शांति दिखाएंगे, भले ही उनकी सहनशीलता एक सीमित सीमा तक सीमित हो। ये लोग मदद करने के लिए तैयार हैं, उन्हें खुश रखने की शक्ति है प्यार से बुलाओ!</strong></p>



<h3 class="has-text-align-center"><strong>तुला</strong></h3>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="500" height="500" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/chakra-1.png" alt="Love Story" class="wp-image-839" title="Real Love | Real Love Story" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/chakra-1.png 500w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/02/chakra-1-300x300.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/02/chakra-1-150x150.png 150w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/02/chakra-1-96x96.png 96w" sizes="(max-width: 500px) 100vw, 500px" /></figure>



<p class="has-medium-font-size"><br><strong>अगर किसी प्रियजन के पास संतुलन है, तो आपके जैसा भाग्यशाली कोई नहीं है, अपने प्रेमी को बहकाने की आपकी इच्छा आपको आहत करती है। एक-दूसरे के सुख-दुख बांटने की कला, समझने की वृत्ति के कारण ऐसा साथी पाकर आप अपने आप को भाग्यशाली समझते हैं। अगर आप उन्हें खुश करना चाहते हैं, तो उन्हें स्पेस दें और उन्हें प्रोत्साहित करें</strong></p>



<h3 class="has-text-align-center"><strong>वृश्चिक</strong></h3>



<p class="has-medium-font-size"><br><strong>यदि आपका प्रेमी या प्रेमिका वृश्चिक राशि का है तो यह व्यक्ति अंतरतम विचारों को लागू नहीं करता है, भले ही वह भावुक हो, अंदर से स्नेही हो। क्रोधित लोगों के मन में गहरे संघर्ष को समझना आवश्यक है, यह है कड़ी मेहनत, दृढ़ता, दृढ़ता को प्रोत्साहित करने के लिए पर्याप्त है।</strong></p>



<h3 class="has-text-align-center"><strong>धनु राशि</strong></h3>



<p class="has-ast-global-color-8-color has-text-color has-medium-font-size"><br><strong>अगर आपका प्रिय व्यक्ति धनु है, तो भगवान का शुक्र है कि आपके जैसा भाग्यशाली कोई नहीं है। धर्मराज में सुखी, चंचल, परोपकारी, आशावादी, प्रेममय, सौम्य, बुद्धिमान, धार्मिक, विनम्र, विनम्र, दयालु, आदर्श राजा, सभी गुण पाए जाते हैं। उनके अच्छे कामों का समर्थन करें ताकि वे खुश रहें।</strong></p>



<h2 class="has-text-align-center"><strong>मकर राशि</strong></h2>



<p class="has-ast-global-color-8-color has-text-color has-medium-font-size"><br><strong>अगर आपका प्रियजन मकर है तो आपको खुश रखने का एक तरीका है उस स्थिति में कैसे खुश रहें, हमेशा मेहनती कैसे रहें नहीं, भले ही वे इतने भावुक न हों, वास्तविकता से अवगत व्यक्ति व्यक्त करना चाहता है सच्चे प्यार में सरल तरीके से, उनके दुख को प्यार की जरूरत होती है।</strong></p>



<h2 class="has-text-align-center"><strong>कुंभ राशि</strong></h2>



<p class="has-ast-global-color-8-color has-text-color has-medium-font-size"><br><strong>यदि आपका प्रेमी या प्रेमिका कुंभ राशि का है तो व्यक्ति यथार्थवादी, गंभीर, बुद्धिमान, अध्ययनशील, गंभीर स्वभाव का होता है। विचारशील प्रकृति वास्तविकता को महत्व देती है हालांकि भावनात्मक नहीं, यह प्यार में सच है।</strong></p>



<h2 class="has-text-align-center"><strong>मीन राशि</strong></h2>



<p class="has-medium-font-size"><br><strong>अगर आपका प्रिय मीन राशि का है तो ये लोग बहुत भावुक, संवेदनशील, हमेशा खुश रहने वाले, प्यार करने वाले स्वभाव वाले, सबका दिल जीतने वाले, उदार, स्वभाव के होते हैं। जो दूसरों की परवाह करता है, जो दिल से प्यार करता है, वह दूसरों के मन में घर बनाने पर अपना ठिकाना भी नहीं जानता। जो लोग भावनात्मक वास्तविकता से पूरी तरह से अनजान हैं वे एक ऐसे व्यक्ति से प्यार करते हैं जो उनके जैसा ही प्यार का नजरिया रखता है। अगर आप इस व्यक्ति को खुश करना चाहते हैं, तो उनका ख्याल रखें, उन्हें दिल से प्यार करें।</strong></p>



<p style="font-size:15px"><strong>इस ब्लॉग को पढ़ने के लिए धन्यवाद!</strong></p>



<p style="font-size:15px"><strong>Other Posts :  ! <a href="/tumacya-premikala-anandi-thevanyaca-mantra/">तुमच्या प्रेमिकाला आनंदी ठेवण्याचा मंत्र.</a>  2) <a href="/find-your-boyfriend-and-girlfriend/">Love | Find Your Real Love | love quotes | love story</a></strong></p>



<p></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/prem-hindi-real-love/">अपनी प्रेमिका को खुश रखने का मंत्र | Love | Love Story | Prem | quotes |  quotes in english | Real Love | Real Love Story | real lover</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Manomay Jyotish</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/prem-hindi-real-love/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Love &#124; Find Your Real Love &#124; love quotes &#124; love story</title>
		<link>/find-your-boyfriend-and-girlfriend/</link>
					<comments>/find-your-boyfriend-and-girlfriend/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 12:46:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[brandi love]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[good morning love]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[i love pdf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[i love you]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[love]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[love images]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[love quotes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[love quotes in english]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[love shayari]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[love shayari in hindi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[love status]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[love story]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[love wallpaper]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lover]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[quotes on love]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[romantic shayari]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[true love quotes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1000</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Find Your Love with Help of Astrology using all Zodiac Signs. Aries Mantra to keep your girlfriend happy. If your boyfriend or girlfriend has Aries zodiac sign, then you have got such a person who is stubborn, fearless, strong, courageous, quick, important. Your loved one is not a stranger but a kind of storm. With &#8230;</p>
<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="/find-your-boyfriend-and-girlfriend/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Love &#124; Find Your Real Love &#124; love quotes &#124; love story</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/find-your-boyfriend-and-girlfriend/">Love | Find Your Real Love | love quotes | love story</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Manomay Jyotish</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h2 class="has-text-align-center">Find Your Love with Help of Astrology using all Zodiac Signs.</h2>



<h3 class="has-text-align-center"><strong>Aries</strong></h3>



<p>Mantra to keep your girlfriend happy. If your boyfriend or girlfriend has Aries zodiac sign, then you have got such a person who is stubborn, fearless, strong, courageous, quick, important. Your loved one is not a stranger but a kind of storm. With that in mind, it&#8217;s hard to understand them, it&#8217;s hard for you to find a lifelong partner, since you are outspoken, outspoken, even if a little bitter, you will be happy to know that their love is sincere.</p>



<h3 class="has-text-align-center"><strong>Taurus</strong></h3>



<p><br>If your boyfriend or girlfriend is from Taurus then your boyfriend or girlfriend is from Taurus. This is their dream, their mind is immersed in love, the thought of constant love is wrapped around them, such a lover or lover loves beauty. Help them with their art skills, help them, sweethearts or lovers do not look back to compliment someone, they also always like to compliment, It is your destiny to find a happy person like Taro Tahi&#8217;s lover or a loving touch is enough.</p>



<h3 class="has-text-align-center"><strong>Gemini</strong></h3>



<p><br>If your boyfriend or girlfriend is Gemini then keep it happy! If your boyfriend or girlfriend is Gemini then you have to admit that you always stay happy and excited because your loved one is very handsome, these people are always thinking of you It is rare for them to make mistakes as they have very good skills, learn from sweet talkers, are very sweet and naughty, constantly win the hearts of others, Gemini lovers think of ways to keep their partner happy, and Dhammal is a fun joke. They also create such an environment, so if your loved one is in Gemini, always chat and have fun!</p>



<h3 class="has-text-align-center"><strong>Cancer</strong></h3>



<p><br>A person who is hungry for love is a person who is hungry for love. Cancer lovers are very loving, compassionate, emotional, affectionate, passionate, flowing in love. These lovers are anxious for love. If such a loving attitude is accompanied, then happiness becomes Mavenasa in the sky.</p>



<p>Cancer loved ones are open-minded and transparent, like water, create happiness and joy in the lives of others, give people the art of living a happy life, very sensitive happy philanthropist with a big heart. If accompanied, they remain happy.</p>



<h3 class="has-text-align-center"><strong>Leo</strong></h3>



<p><br>If a loved one is a Leo, then the person who has a flamboyant personality is a Leo, every Ada is like a king. It is as if Moden is a principle that will not bend, even in humiliation, these people are plates. Give!</p>



<h3 class="has-text-align-center"><strong>Virgo</strong></h3>



<p><br>How to keep your loved one happy if you are in Virgo? Virgo loved ones are always worried about your partner. They think about what they don&#8217;t want, their interests are always on top, their love never fails, it is difficult to find a person with a very loving and tender heart! No matter how many mistakes your mate may make, these people will show you the kindness, forgiveness, and peace they have, even though their tolerance is limited to a limited extent. These people are ready to help, the power to keep them happy is to call with love!</p>



<h3 class="has-text-align-center"><strong>Libra</strong></h3>



<p><br>If a loved one has a balance, then there is no one as lucky as you, your desire to seduce your lover hurts you. You consider yourself lucky to have found such a mate because of the art of sharing each other&#8217;s joys and sorrows, the attitude of understanding. If you want to make them happy, give them space and encourage them</p>



<h3 class="has-text-align-center"><strong>Scorpio</strong></h3>



<p><br>If your boyfriend or girlfriend is Scorpio, then this person does not apply the innermost thoughts, even though he is passionate, he is affectionate on the inside. It is necessary to understand the deep struggles in the minds of those who are angry, it is enough to encourage hard work, perseverance, perseverance.</p>



<h3 class="has-text-align-center"><strong>Sagittarius</strong></h3>



<p><br>If your loved one is Sagittarius, thank God there is no one as lucky as you. Happy, playful, philanthropic, optimistic, loving, gentle, intelligent, religious, humble, humble, compassionate, ideal king, all the qualities are found in Dharmaraja. . Support the good deeds they have so that they will be happy.</p>



<h3 class="has-text-align-center"><strong>Capricorn</strong></h3>



<p><br>If your loved one is Capricorn then there is a way to keep you happy. How to be happy in that situation, how to always be industrious No, even though they are not so passionate, a person who is aware of the reality wants to express true love in a simple way, their sadness needs love.</p>



<h3 class="has-text-align-center"><strong>Aquarius</strong></h3>



<p><br>If your boyfriend or girlfriend is Aquarius then the person is realistic, serious, intelligent, studious, serious in nature. Thoughtful nature gives importance to reality. Though not emotional, it is true in love.</p>



<h3 class="has-text-align-center"><strong>Pisces</strong></h3>



<p><br>If your loved one is Pisces then these people are very emotional, sensitive, always happy, loving nature, winning everyone&#8217;s heart, generous, temperament. The one who cares for others, who loves with all his heart, does not even know his whereabouts when he makes a home in the mind of others. People who are completely unaware of the very emotional reality love a person who has the same attitude of love as them. If you want to make this person happy, take care of them, love them from the heart.</p>



<p>Thanks for reading this <strong>blog</strong>!</p>



<p>Be sure to let us know your feedback.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/find-your-boyfriend-and-girlfriend/">Love | Find Your Real Love | love quotes | love story</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Manomay Jyotish</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/find-your-boyfriend-and-girlfriend/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
