<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Todays Archives - Manomay Jyotish</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/todays/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Manomay Jyotish</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 12:31:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/icon.jpg</url>
	<title>Todays Archives - Manomay Jyotish</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Rahu-Ketu change &#8211; Tul Rasa</title>
		<link>/rahu-ketu-change-tul-rasa/</link>
					<comments>/rahu-ketu-change-tul-rasa/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 12:29:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Astrology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jyotish]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ketu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[planetary zodiac]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rahu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rahu and Ketu]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Saturn]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Todays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Todays Horoscope]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1031</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>  Rahu Rahu-Ketu inauspiciousness will reduce the intensity of saturn Hello!   We always analyze the planetary zodiac changes and their effects from time to time. Accordingly, we are studying two planets J Rahu and Ketu which will change in the coming April month on 12th April. Rahu will enter Aries from Taurus and Ketu &#8230;</p>
<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="/rahu-ketu-change-tul-rasa/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Rahu-Ketu change &#8211; Tul Rasa</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rahu-ketu-change-tul-rasa/">Rahu-Ketu change &#8211; Tul Rasa</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Manomay Jyotish</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p> </p>
<div>
<h3><strong>Rahu</strong></h3>
<p><strong>Rahu-Ketu inauspiciousness</strong></p>
<p><strong>will reduce the intensity of saturn</strong></p>
<p><strong>Hello!</strong></p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>We always analyze the planetary zodiac changes and their effects from time to time. Accordingly, we are studying two planets J Rahu and Ketu which will change in the coming April month on 12th April. Rahu will enter Aries from Taurus and Ketu will enter Libra from Scorpio. What effect will they actually have? We are studying it according to the zodiac. What will be the effect of this change on Libra today? We will understand this in detail. #rahuketuparivartan</strong></p>
<p><strong>To understand the importance of Rahu and Ketu&#8217;s change of zodiac, we have to first understand the information of these two planets. Suppose Venus is a planet along with Rahu in a native&#8217;s journal, then it will work to create ownership in the mind of the native. How should my partner be? How smart must that be? Should he be tactful or should he talk to others or not? The planet representing all these things is Rahu. Ketu has opposite mindset. This will work even if the spouse is pregnant. It will work no matter what. A person with no color combination can also love someone. Because in the caste of such castes there is a combination of Ketu and Venus. The special thing is that the world of such castes is also very good. Because Ketu does not care about these things.</strong></p>
<p><strong>Although the planets Rahu and Ketu are related to each other, they are both at different ends. Therefore, their effect is also opposite to each other. We can call Rahu the misery of Kaal. This is a shadow planet. He has a tendency to take revenge. It is also believed to be the cause of alcoholism and other bad habits. Accidents, theft, accidents, dacoity, displacement are all considered factors. But this does not completely spoil Rahu. He has some good stuff too. Rahu means to achieve something by working hard. Rahu means getting something quickly, enjoying material pleasures to the fullest. Therefore, in today&#8217;s 21st century, Rahu is of great importance in today&#8217;s modern era.</strong></p>
<p><strong>The planet Ketu has the opposite effect. It is the planet of liberation. Ketu is doing the work of taking man on the path of spirituality. If Ketu is strong in the horoscope of a person, then that person gets away from all the temptations of life. He is different than all. The causative planet of spirituality is actually three. These three planets are Saturn, Jupiter and Ketu. But there is a fundamental difference between these three. That is, Shani Maharaj tells the caste to behave with morality, justice and go towards salvation. Guru Maharaj tells Jataka that first complete all the actions, all the obligations and move towards salvation. So Ketu tells Jataka to renounce everything and move towards salvation. Of course Ketu is a planet that somewhere denies responsibility, we can say. Its effects are terrifying. Where he sits in the magazine, he works to create distance in the relationship. He is trying to destroy the causality of the planet he is sitting with. It also makes a distinction between the position in which it is sighted. Man gets bored because of the planet Ketu. So Rahu and Ketu&#8217;s zodiac sign is happening on 12th April. Rahu will enter Taurus from Aries and Ketu will enter Libra from Scorpio. What will be the effect of this change on Libra? Let us understand it now. </strong></p>
<p><strong> Looking at Libra, the arrival of Rahu will be in your seventh place. Also Ketu will arrive in your zodiac. Because these two planets change zodiac at the same time. Both start their journey at 180 degrees from each other and with rotational motion. Actually, these two planets are not points and their journey starts from a curved path. The impact of this visit is huge. Because both these planets are sitting firmly in the same zodiac for one and a half years. That is, Rahu and Ketu are the longest-lasting planets after Saturn in a zodiac. So this Rahu is in your seventh and Ketu is in your zodiac. They are showing a different kind of struggle in your life. I will also tell you the results of this struggle. However, Tul caste people should not be afraid of this. Because during this time Shani Maharaj is going to help you a lot. Therefore it is necessary to consider not only the fruits of Rahu-Ketu but also the auspicious results of Shani Maharaj or even Guru Maharaj. We will tell you that separately according to the amount.</strong></p>
<p><strong>Looking at the effect of Rahu, Rahu situated in the seventh house works to increase the ego of the partner somewhere. Takes your partner away from you or creates hatred between the two. At the same time, he loses family health. disturbs the peace of the family. So you have to take proper care of it. The world has said that a vessel must contain a vessel. However, it will be very important for you to take care that no controversy should arise. As you know Rahu has total three aspects: fifth, seventh and ninth. That is, he is seated at one place and his vision falling at three places is affected by the position of Rahu at four places. Accordingly, the fifth aspect of Rahu in the seventh position will move to the eleventh position. The eleventh place in the magazine is known as the place of profit and fulfillment of desires. After that the seventh sight will fall on your zodiac sign which is the first place and the ninth sight will fall on the third place which means strength and hard work. From the point of view of Rahu, being in the position of wish fulfillment from the seventh house, Rahu acts to not let your wishes come true or give everything other than what you want. Because their role is mainly in the case of non-fulfillment of their wishes.</strong></p>
<p><strong>The sight falling on Rahu&#8217;s zodiac will increase anger in your mind. At the same time, frustration can also increase. Because Ketu is also sitting there. The planet Ketu is the cause of depression. Your role will be to ignore a question or remain silent on something. You will have to face a lot of difficulties for this role. Because when we are constantly persecuted, wronged, harassed or harassed by our relatives, we are constantly thinking in our mind. In fact, it&#8217;s completely out of mind. Then somewhere its efficiency decreases. This could happen to you. Because in the week, the sight of Rahu will also fall at the place of your labor. From there he will work to remove your shortcomings. But even if all this is true, then the most important thing is that on April 29, Shani Maharaj will change your zodiac and enter your fifth place. From there his third vision will fall on Rahu. Saturn and Rahu are friendly planets. Also, Shani Maharaj is the Raja Yogakaraka planet of your magazine. Therefore Shani Maharaj will work to reduce the intensity of all the ill effects of Rahu that I have just told you. So it won&#8217;t bother you much. #bestastrologerinmaharashtra</strong></p>
<p><strong>In case of Ketu change, the coming of Ketu in your zodiac will work to change your thinking. This will constantly fill your mind with negative thoughts. All the bad things that are happening in the world are happening with me, this feeling will be formed in your mind. Whenever this feeling arises in your mind, I am giving you a suggestion that you should remember the dialogue between Karna and Lord Krishna at such a time. Which I also mentioned in some videos at that time. In this, Karna says, &#8220;Why all this happened to me? I was born and abandoned by my mother. what&#8217;s wrong with me? With this he presented all the miseries of life in front of Lord Krishna. Then Lord Krishna says to him, &#8220;You are telling this to a person who was planned to kill before birth. He was taken away from his mother as soon as he was born.&#8221; This is how Lord Krishna tries to calm his mind by telling him everything.</strong></p>
<p><strong>Accordingly, &#8216;Why in my case?&#8217; When you say so, you really have no right to say it. Because at that time many other auspicious works were done only in your case. Therefore Tul castes are specially advised to control their mind. Ketu coming to the zodiac and marriage place will try to take you away from you. Will try to create disappointment in the mind. In such an adverse situation, you have to overcome all these things of your own free will and move towards progress. Shani Maharaj will definitely help you in this work.  Overall even though it may have a negative effect on Tul castes but with the help of Shani Maharaj you are going to have a successful journey.</strong></p>
<p><strong>I think this information is sufficient to understand the effect of Rahu-Ketu change on Libra. So let&#8217;s stop here in today&#8217;s episode. In the next section, we will study the effects on the next zodiac sign. So let&#8217;s see you again in the next part.</strong></p>
<p><strong>Thank you!</strong></p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>Good luck!</strong></p>
<p><strong>Visit More : <a href="https://www.manomayjyotish.com/blog/">Blogs</a> | <a href="http://www.manomayjyotish.com/about-us/">About Us</a> | <a href="http://m.youtube.com/c/manomayjyotish/">Youtube</a></strong></p>
</div>

<figure class="wp-block-post-featured-image"><img loading="lazy" width="428" height="338" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Rahu-And-Ketu-Images.jpg" class="attachment-post-thumbnail size-post-thumbnail wp-post-image" alt="Rahu-Ketu change &#8211; Tul Rasa" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Rahu-And-Ketu-Images.jpg 428w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/03/Rahu-And-Ketu-Images-300x237.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 428px) 100vw, 428px" /></figure><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rahu-ketu-change-tul-rasa/">Rahu-Ketu change &#8211; Tul Rasa</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Manomay Jyotish</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/rahu-ketu-change-tul-rasa/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
